<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<search>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>The analysis of Electric-motorcycle(Yadea-Y1S)in the UK market</title>
    <link href="/2022/11/14/Yadea_analysis/"/>
    <url>/2022/11/14/Yadea_analysis/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>The Market Audit:</strong> </p><p><strong>Summary:</strong></p><p>Our product is going to be sold in the UK which has a mature infrastructure for its communication and transportation system. The company also needs to be concerned about the price, quality, design, brand, and environmental benefits it can bring to society. All these factors including the after-sales service can affect consumers’ purchasing habits. The distribution of the products which includes 30+ UK deals of scootersise mainly established in the England of the UK. Besides the important role of online marketing in social media, finding agent middlemen, wholesalers and retailers can also have a huge impact on increasing the sales of Yadea’s Y1S.</p><h4 id="Describe-the-market-in-which-the-product-is-to-be-sold"><a href="#Describe-the-market-in-which-the-product-is-to-be-sold" class="headerlink" title="Describe the market in which the product is to be sold"></a>Describe the market in which the product is to be sold</h4><h5 id="1-Geographical-region"><a href="#1-Geographical-region" class="headerlink" title="1. Geographical region:"></a>1. Geographical region:</h5><ul><li> The United Kingdom which comprises England, Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland locates in the Western part of the European countries which is surrounded by four seas. To the South is the English Channel, which separates it from continental Europe. to the East by the North Sea, and to the West by the Irish Sea and the Atlantic Ocean. The land has a total area of 243,610 km² and a total coastline of 12,429 km. </li></ul><h5 id="2-Forms-of-transportation-and-communication-available-in-that-region"><a href="#2-Forms-of-transportation-and-communication-available-in-that-region" class="headerlink" title="2. Forms of transportation and communication available in that region"></a>2. Forms of transportation and communication available in that region</h5><ul><li><p>Cycling is very popular in the UK which can both save money and keep you fit. Most UK towns and cities offer regular bus services and Taxis are easy to find in all major cities and towns also the UK has a large train network to travel across cities and towns. There are also 24 international airports in the UK which provide a variety of cheap flights. In addition, Eurostar’s high-speed train services running frequently can travel from London to the continent in just over two hours, every day of the week. </p></li><li><p>Under the country code +44, there were a total of 111.04 million connections in 2020. Among them were 79.01 million mobile phones, which corresponds to an average of 1.2 per person[<a href="#_ftn1">1]</a>. In addition to broadband Internet connections, around 95% of all residents have access to the Internet. Around 41% have a fast Internet connection.</p></li></ul><h5 id="3-Consumer-buying-habits"><a href="#3-Consumer-buying-habits" class="headerlink" title="3. Consumer buying habits"></a>3. Consumer buying habits</h5><p>a.   Ecological and responsible consumption is growing, highly adaptable, and expandable, the Y1S can be modified for bike-sharing, takeaway operations, logistics, and other applications.</p><p>b.   The customers would care about the price, quality, design, brand, and environmental benefits it can bring to society. After-sales service should also be considered, and claims are common if the product has some problems.</p><p>c.   The British are increasingly buying online, thus online commerce is an important market. Social networks are also important in the purchase decision. The number of social media users is equivalent to 84.3% of the total population and Facebook is the main network. Thus Yasea Y1S can also choose to promote its products through the channel of social media.</p><h5 id="4-Distribution-of-the-product"><a href="#4-Distribution-of-the-product" class="headerlink" title="4. Distribution of the product"></a>4. Distribution of the product</h5><p>a.   Typical retail outlets: There are 40000+ retailers and 3000+ distributors across the world. There are around 30+ UK deals of scooters that can be found in the England of the UK and there is also one that can be found in Whales.</p><p>b.   Product sales by other middlemen: Finding agent middlemen for the scooter is a good approach to selling the product. Using Wholesalers who bought in more quantities and sell them to the retailer can also increase the chances of buying the scooter.</p><h5 id="5-Advertising-and-promotion"><a href="#5-Advertising-and-promotion" class="headerlink" title="5. Advertising and promotion"></a>5. Advertising and promotion</h5><p>a.   Advertising media: Facebook and Instagram are good tools for using the market strategy called Market push and pull. The algorithm technology can push the products to our potential customers and bring their interests into our YADEA Y1S.</p><p>b.   Types of discounts available: In this case, using the percentage sales and early payment discounts can be a good method. The shops can offer the customer a 10 to 15 percent discount if they buy the cars within the promotion activity. Those who paid for the car early in the limited time will get more discount. </p><h3 id="The-Marketing-Plan"><a href="#The-Marketing-Plan" class="headerlink" title="The Marketing Plan:"></a><strong>The Marketing Plan:</strong></h3><p><strong>Summary:</strong></p><p>Yadea-Y1S targets the high-end market for the businessman to use and it is important to find the right customer in a short time. The UK market has the potential to grow in the future but to gain a competitive advantage in the market share, the company needs to expand its retail shops in the UK to attract more customers who the interests in using the electric motor car in life. Besides that, marketing techniques for example using coupons and personal selling will be helpful as well. Through estimation Yadea’s net income forecast is expected an average of $401.2 million over the next five fiscal years. To maximize the probability of achieving this target, the company can use the SWOT analysis to know that as a listed company its strength is the diversification of the products provided to the customers and its weakness is the business model which can be imitated by its opponents, its opportunities are the strong research and development team and the threat can be the international competitors and the political risk and policies that will affect the operation abroad. The product advantages and features are the large battery capacity and the intelligent Battery Management System, it is also dedicated to providing sustainable customer service together with its distributor partners. Our Wish is to increase Yadea’s leadership role in the industry, by creating a new generation that’s identified by a green commuting lifestyle.</p><h4 id="A-Marketing-objectives"><a href="#A-Marketing-objectives" class="headerlink" title="A.  Marketing objectives"></a>A.  Marketing objectives</h4><h5 id="1-Target-market-As-the-products-of-Yadea-Group-provide-a-superior-value-proposition-it-should-segment-the-customers-based-on-two-main-demographic-criteria-–-income-of-the-prospective-customer-and-the-life-cycle-stage-Yadea-Y1S-is-categorized-as-a-commercial-electric-motor-car-it-may-target-the-high-end-market-for-the-businessman-to-use-and-the-life-cycle-of-the-product-is-short-for-around-5-years-as-it-is-a-specialty-good-Thus-it-is-of-great-importance-to-advertising-our-products-to-the-exact-consumers-in-a-short-time"><a href="#1-Target-market-As-the-products-of-Yadea-Group-provide-a-superior-value-proposition-it-should-segment-the-customers-based-on-two-main-demographic-criteria-–-income-of-the-prospective-customer-and-the-life-cycle-stage-Yadea-Y1S-is-categorized-as-a-commercial-electric-motor-car-it-may-target-the-high-end-market-for-the-businessman-to-use-and-the-life-cycle-of-the-product-is-short-for-around-5-years-as-it-is-a-specialty-good-Thus-it-is-of-great-importance-to-advertising-our-products-to-the-exact-consumers-in-a-short-time" class="headerlink" title="1. Target market: As the products of Yadea Group provide a superior value proposition, it should segment the customers based on two main demographic criteria – income of the prospective customer and the life cycle stage. Yadea-Y1S is categorized as a commercial electric motor car, it may target the high-end market for the businessman to use, and the life cycle of the product is short for around 5 years as it is a specialty good. Thus it is of great importance to advertising our products to the exact consumers in a short time."></a>1. Target market: As the products of Yadea Group provide a superior value proposition, it should segment the customers based on two main demographic criteria – income of the prospective customer and the life cycle stage. Yadea-Y1S is categorized as a commercial electric motor car, it may target the high-end market for the businessman to use, and the life cycle of the product is short for around 5 years as it is a specialty good. Thus it is of great importance to advertising our products to the exact consumers in a short time.</h5><p><img src="file:////Users/dianazhang/Library/Group%20Containers/UBF8T346G9.Office/TemporaryItems/msohtmlclip/clip_image001.png" alt="A picture containing bar chart  Description automatically generated"></p><h5 id="2-Sales-forecast-years-1-5-Global-e-scooter-sales-in-2021-have-been-6-1million-up-12-4-from-the-previous-year-with-sales-growth-declining-in-the-second-half-when-they-were-stable-over-the-correspondent-period-in-2020-Currently-operating-in-over-80-nations-however-98-of-sales-are-done-in-China-The-UK-market-has-the-potential-to-grow-in-the-future-but-to-be-the-first-mover-and-have-a-competitive-advantage-in-the-market-share-the-company-needs-to-expand-its-retail-shops-in-the-UK-To-attract-more-customers-to-know-the-product-and-the-brand-which-brings-the-interest-in-using-the-electric-motor-car-in-life"><a href="#2-Sales-forecast-years-1-5-Global-e-scooter-sales-in-2021-have-been-6-1million-up-12-4-from-the-previous-year-with-sales-growth-declining-in-the-second-half-when-they-were-stable-over-the-correspondent-period-in-2020-Currently-operating-in-over-80-nations-however-98-of-sales-are-done-in-China-The-UK-market-has-the-potential-to-grow-in-the-future-but-to-be-the-first-mover-and-have-a-competitive-advantage-in-the-market-share-the-company-needs-to-expand-its-retail-shops-in-the-UK-To-attract-more-customers-to-know-the-product-and-the-brand-which-brings-the-interest-in-using-the-electric-motor-car-in-life" class="headerlink" title="2. Sales forecast years 1-5: Global e-scooter sales in 2021 have been 6.1million, up 12.4% from the previous year, with sales growth declining in the second half when they were stable over the correspondent period in 2020. Currently operating in over 80 nations however 98% of sales are done in China. The UK market has the potential to grow in the future but to be the first mover and have a competitive advantage in the market share, the company needs to expand its retail shops in the UK. To attract more customers to know the product and the brand which brings the interest in using the electric motor car in life."></a>2. Sales forecast years 1-5: Global e-scooter sales in 2021 have been 6.1million, up 12.4% from the previous year, with sales growth declining in the second half when they were stable over the correspondent period in 2020. Currently operating in over 80 nations however 98% of sales are done in China. The UK market has the potential to grow in the future but to be the first mover and have a competitive advantage in the market share, the company needs to expand its retail shops in the UK. To attract more customers to know the product and the brand which brings the interest in using the electric motor car in life.</h5><h5 id="3-Profit-forecast-years-1-5-Yadea’s-net-income-forecast-in-2022-will-be-275-9-million-Yadea’s-net-income-forecast-is-expected-an-average-of-401-2-million-over-the-next-five-fiscal-years-2"><a href="#3-Profit-forecast-years-1-5-Yadea’s-net-income-forecast-in-2022-will-be-275-9-million-Yadea’s-net-income-forecast-is-expected-an-average-of-401-2-million-over-the-next-five-fiscal-years-2" class="headerlink" title="3. Profit forecast years 1-5: Yadea’s net income forecast in 2022 will be $275.9 million. Yadea’s net income forecast is expected an average of 401.2 million over the next five fiscal years[2]."></a>3. Profit forecast years 1-5: Yadea’s net income forecast in 2022 will be $275.9 million. Yadea’s net income forecast is expected an average of 401.2 million over the next five fiscal years[<a href="#_ftn2">2]</a>.</h5><p>![Screenshot 2022-11-14 at 4.20.04 PM](../img/Screenshot 2022-11-14 at 4.20.04 PM.png)</p><h5 id="4-Market-penetration-and-coverage-Moreover-with-the-emergence-of-demand-for-personalized-green-micro-mobility-continuous-upgrade-of-electric-two-wheeled-vehicles-and-diversification-of-product-applications-the-customer-base-will-continue-to-expand-Further-coupled-with-the-sustainable-replacement-demand-brought-by-the-growing-penetration-of-two-wheeled-vehicles-the-two-wheeled-vehicles-industry-enjoys-an-optimistic-outlook"><a href="#4-Market-penetration-and-coverage-Moreover-with-the-emergence-of-demand-for-personalized-green-micro-mobility-continuous-upgrade-of-electric-two-wheeled-vehicles-and-diversification-of-product-applications-the-customer-base-will-continue-to-expand-Further-coupled-with-the-sustainable-replacement-demand-brought-by-the-growing-penetration-of-two-wheeled-vehicles-the-two-wheeled-vehicles-industry-enjoys-an-optimistic-outlook" class="headerlink" title="4. Market penetration and coverage: Moreover, with the emergence of demand for personalized green micro-mobility, continuous upgrade of electric two-wheeled vehicles, and diversification of product applications, the customer base will continue to expand. Further coupled with the sustainable replacement demand brought by the growing penetration of two-wheeled vehicles, the two-wheeled vehicles industry enjoys an optimistic outlook."></a>4. Market penetration and coverage: Moreover, with the emergence of demand for personalized green micro-mobility, continuous upgrade of electric two-wheeled vehicles, and diversification of product applications, the customer base will continue to expand. Further coupled with the sustainable replacement demand brought by the growing penetration of two-wheeled vehicles, the two-wheeled vehicles industry enjoys an optimistic outlook.</h5><h4 id="B-SWOT-Analysis"><a href="#B-SWOT-Analysis" class="headerlink" title="B.  SWOT Analysis"></a>B.  SWOT Analysis</h4><h5 id="1-Strengths-Brands-catering-to-different-customer-segments-within-the-Recreational-Products-segment-The-Group-offers-a-wide-range-of-electric-scooters-and-electric-bicycles-with-diverse-designs-styles-and-functionalities-catering-to-the-needs-of-a-broad-customer-base-the-Group-had-56-models-of-electric-scooters-and-69-models-of-electric-bicycles-for-customers-to-choose-from"><a href="#1-Strengths-Brands-catering-to-different-customer-segments-within-the-Recreational-Products-segment-The-Group-offers-a-wide-range-of-electric-scooters-and-electric-bicycles-with-diverse-designs-styles-and-functionalities-catering-to-the-needs-of-a-broad-customer-base-the-Group-had-56-models-of-electric-scooters-and-69-models-of-electric-bicycles-for-customers-to-choose-from" class="headerlink" title="1. Strengths: Brands catering to different customer segments within the Recreational Products segment - The Group offers a wide range of electric scooters and electric bicycles with diverse designs, styles, and functionalities catering to the needs of a broad customer base. the Group had 56 models of electric scooters and 69 models of electric bicycles for customers to choose from."></a>1. Strengths: Brands catering to different customer segments within the Recreational Products segment - The Group offers a wide range of electric scooters and electric bicycles with diverse designs, styles, and functionalities catering to the needs of a broad customer base. the Group had 56 models of electric scooters and 69 models of electric bicycles for customers to choose from.</h5><h5 id="2-Weaknesses-The-Business-Model-of-Yadea-Group-can-be-easily-imitated-by-competitors-in-the-Recreational-Products-industry-To-overcome-these-challenges-company-needs-to-build-a-platform-model-that-can-integrate-suppliers-vendors-and-end-users"><a href="#2-Weaknesses-The-Business-Model-of-Yadea-Group-can-be-easily-imitated-by-competitors-in-the-Recreational-Products-industry-To-overcome-these-challenges-company-needs-to-build-a-platform-model-that-can-integrate-suppliers-vendors-and-end-users" class="headerlink" title="2. Weaknesses: The Business Model of Yadea Group can be easily imitated by competitors in the Recreational Products industry. To overcome these challenges company needs to build a platform model that can integrate suppliers, vendors, and end users."></a>2. Weaknesses: The Business Model of Yadea Group can be easily imitated by competitors in the Recreational Products industry. To overcome these challenges company needs to build a platform model that can integrate suppliers, vendors, and end users.</h5><h5 id="3-Opportunities-The-Group-had-an-annual-electric-two-wheeled-vehicle-production-capacity-of-approximately-17-million-units-supported-by-more-than-9-000-employees-Accelerated-technological-innovations-and-advances-It-also-has-a-strong-research-and-development-team-based-in-Shanghai-and-Wuxi-with-906-research-and-development-professionals-with-various-product-design-backgrounds-for-electric-two-wheeled-vehicles-Also-the-Company-was-listed-on-the-Main-Board-of-The-Stock-Exchange-of-Hong-Kong-which-will-increase-its-financing-capital-for-its-operation"><a href="#3-Opportunities-The-Group-had-an-annual-electric-two-wheeled-vehicle-production-capacity-of-approximately-17-million-units-supported-by-more-than-9-000-employees-Accelerated-technological-innovations-and-advances-It-also-has-a-strong-research-and-development-team-based-in-Shanghai-and-Wuxi-with-906-research-and-development-professionals-with-various-product-design-backgrounds-for-electric-two-wheeled-vehicles-Also-the-Company-was-listed-on-the-Main-Board-of-The-Stock-Exchange-of-Hong-Kong-which-will-increase-its-financing-capital-for-its-operation" class="headerlink" title="3. Opportunities: The Group had an annual electric two-wheeled vehicle production capacity of approximately 17 million units, supported by more than 9,000 employees. Accelerated technological innovations and advances -It also has a strong research and development team based in Shanghai and Wuxi with 906 research and development professionals with various product design backgrounds for electric two-wheeled vehicles. Also, the Company was listed on the Main Board of The Stock Exchange of Hong Kong which will increase its financing capital for its operation."></a>3. Opportunities: The Group had an annual electric two-wheeled vehicle production capacity of approximately 17 million units, supported by more than 9,000 employees. Accelerated technological innovations and advances -It also has a strong research and development team based in Shanghai and Wuxi with 906 research and development professionals with various product design backgrounds for electric two-wheeled vehicles. Also, the Company was listed on the Main Board of The Stock Exchange of Hong Kong which will increase its financing capital for its operation.</h5><h5 id="4-Threats-Competitors-catching-up-with-the-product-development-Even-though-at-present-the-Yadea-Group-is-still-the-leader-in-product-innovation-in-the-Recreational-Products-segment-It-is-facing-stiff-challenges-from-international-and-local-competitors-The-changing-policy-and-the-external-political-risk-might-affect-the-operation-in-the-UK-thus-the-managers-have-to-follow-up-with-the-macroeconomic-of-the-society-to-adjust-its-marketing-strategy"><a href="#4-Threats-Competitors-catching-up-with-the-product-development-Even-though-at-present-the-Yadea-Group-is-still-the-leader-in-product-innovation-in-the-Recreational-Products-segment-It-is-facing-stiff-challenges-from-international-and-local-competitors-The-changing-policy-and-the-external-political-risk-might-affect-the-operation-in-the-UK-thus-the-managers-have-to-follow-up-with-the-macroeconomic-of-the-society-to-adjust-its-marketing-strategy" class="headerlink" title="4. Threats: Competitors catching up with the product development - Even though at present the Yadea Group is still the leader in product innovation in the Recreational Products segment. It is facing stiff challenges from international and local competitors. The changing policy and the external political risk might affect the operation in the UK, thus the managers have to follow up with the macroeconomic of the society to adjust its marketing strategy."></a>4. Threats: Competitors catching up with the product development - Even though at present the Yadea Group is still the leader in product innovation in the Recreational Products segment. It is facing stiff challenges from international and local competitors. The changing policy and the external political risk might affect the operation in the UK, thus the managers have to follow up with the macroeconomic of the society to adjust its marketing strategy.</h5><h4 id="C-Product-adaptation-or-modification"><a href="#C-Product-adaptation-or-modification" class="headerlink" title="C.  Product adaptation or modification"></a>C.  Product adaptation or modification</h4><h5 id="1-Core-component-The-two-detachable-lightweight-dual-connected-batteries-offer-large-battery-capacity-and-the-vehicle-also-allows-for-two-intelligent-charging-modes-–-direct-from-the-vehicle-or-charging-from-the-battery-base-so-riders-can-go-further-for-more-convenient-operation-At-the-same-time-Yadea’s-intelligent-Battery-Management-System-BMS-ensures-a-safer-ride-with-protection-against-overcurrent-overheating-overcharging-short-circuiting-and-more"><a href="#1-Core-component-The-two-detachable-lightweight-dual-connected-batteries-offer-large-battery-capacity-and-the-vehicle-also-allows-for-two-intelligent-charging-modes-–-direct-from-the-vehicle-or-charging-from-the-battery-base-so-riders-can-go-further-for-more-convenient-operation-At-the-same-time-Yadea’s-intelligent-Battery-Management-System-BMS-ensures-a-safer-ride-with-protection-against-overcurrent-overheating-overcharging-short-circuiting-and-more" class="headerlink" title="1. Core component:  The two detachable, lightweight dual-connected batteries offer large battery capacity, and the vehicle also allows for two intelligent charging modes – direct from the vehicle or charging from the battery base, so riders can go further for more convenient operation. At the same time, Yadea’s intelligent Battery Management System (BMS) ensures a safer ride with protection against overcurrent, overheating, overcharging, short-circuiting, and more."></a>1. Core component:  The two detachable, lightweight dual-connected batteries offer large battery capacity, and the vehicle also allows for two intelligent charging modes – direct from the vehicle or charging from the battery base, so riders can go further for more convenient operation. At the same time, Yadea’s intelligent Battery Management System (BMS) ensures a safer ride with protection against overcurrent, overheating, overcharging, short-circuiting, and more.</h5><h5 id="2-Packaging-component-Domestic-waste-is-handed-over-to-the-local-environmental-sanitation-department-for-regular-treatment-every-month-while-waste-packaging-materials-are-handed-over-to-a-third-party-agency-for-recycling-and-reuse-to-achieve-resource-recycling"><a href="#2-Packaging-component-Domestic-waste-is-handed-over-to-the-local-environmental-sanitation-department-for-regular-treatment-every-month-while-waste-packaging-materials-are-handed-over-to-a-third-party-agency-for-recycling-and-reuse-to-achieve-resource-recycling" class="headerlink" title="2. Packaging component: Domestic waste is handed over to the local environmental sanitation department for regular treatment every month, while waste packaging materials are handed over to a third-party agency for recycling and reuse to achieve resource recycling."></a>2. Packaging component: Domestic waste is handed over to the local environmental sanitation department for regular treatment every month, while waste packaging materials are handed over to a third-party agency for recycling and reuse to achieve resource recycling.</h5><h5 id="3-Support-services-component-At-the-same-time-the-Group-will-provide-distributors-with-training-in-technical-support-distributor-product-shopping-guide-store-management-event-promotion-including-after-sales-training-and-maintenance-support-and-promote-the-concept-of-sustainable-customer-service-together-with-distributor-partners-to-ensure-that-distributors-can-provide-customers-with-good-sales-and-after-sales-experience-and-promote-high-standard-service-requirements-to-overseas-distributors"><a href="#3-Support-services-component-At-the-same-time-the-Group-will-provide-distributors-with-training-in-technical-support-distributor-product-shopping-guide-store-management-event-promotion-including-after-sales-training-and-maintenance-support-and-promote-the-concept-of-sustainable-customer-service-together-with-distributor-partners-to-ensure-that-distributors-can-provide-customers-with-good-sales-and-after-sales-experience-and-promote-high-standard-service-requirements-to-overseas-distributors" class="headerlink" title="3. Support services component: At the same time, the Group will provide distributors with training in technical support, distributor product shopping guide, store management, event promotion (including after-sales training and maintenance support), and promote the concept of sustainable customer service together with distributor partners to ensure that distributors can provide customers with good sales and after-sales experience, and promote high-standard service requirements to overseas distributors."></a>3. Support services component: At the same time, the Group will provide distributors with training in technical support, distributor product shopping guide, store management, event promotion (including after-sales training and maintenance support), and promote the concept of sustainable customer service together with distributor partners to ensure that distributors can provide customers with good sales and after-sales experience, and promote high-standard service requirements to overseas distributors.</h5><h4 id="D-Promotion-mix"><a href="#D-Promotion-mix" class="headerlink" title="D.  Promotion mix"></a>D.  Promotion mix</h4><h5 id="1-Advertising"><a href="#1-Advertising" class="headerlink" title="1. Advertising"></a>1. Advertising</h5><p>a.   Objectives: Yadea Group is a high-end electric two-wheeler manufacturer integrating the development, production, and sales of pedelec, electric mopeds, electric motorcycles, electric kick scooters, and their accessories.</p><p>b.   Media mix: Digital marketing can be targeted on Instagram, Facebook, and YouTube; while traditional marketing can be transit signage, direct mail, and TV and radio spots.</p><p>c.   Message: Our Wish is to increase Yadea’s leadership role in the industry, by creating a new generation that’s identified by a green commuting lifestyle.</p><p>d.   Costs: From Yadea’s 2021 financial annual report, the advertising expense is increasing from 281,937,000 RMB in 2020 to <strong>364,720,000 RMB</strong> in 2021.</p><h5 id="2-Sales-promotion"><a href="#2-Sales-promotion" class="headerlink" title="2. Sales promotion"></a>2. Sales promotion</h5><p>a.   Objectives: We Promise-Provide a convenient, safe, free and comfortable ultimate riding experience for our customers.</p><p>b.   Coupons: You can get the promotion code from the online website and then you can get a discount on the product Yadea Y1S. If not, the coupons can also be achieved from the promotion activities.</p><p>c.   Premiums: The main measures can include random inspection of the fire-fighting facilities in the distributor’s warehouses from time to time, promotion of explosion-proof cabinets for lithium batteries in stores, promotion of storage of batteries and other goods in different areas, purchase of relevant insurance, and organizing relevant training.</p><p>d.   Costs: Selling and distribution expenses increased by approximately 37.2% from RMB934.9 million in 2020 to RMB1,282.9 million in 2021, primarily due to the increase in employee benefits expenses, advertising expenses, and travel expenses.</p><h5 id="3-Personal-selling-First-can-build-up-the-brand-recognition-and-product-awareness-of-Yadea-Y1S-then-stimulate-the-customer’s-demand-by-building-a-relationship-at-the-same-time-persuading-and-providing-technical-information-about-the-electric-motorbike"><a href="#3-Personal-selling-First-can-build-up-the-brand-recognition-and-product-awareness-of-Yadea-Y1S-then-stimulate-the-customer’s-demand-by-building-a-relationship-at-the-same-time-persuading-and-providing-technical-information-about-the-electric-motorbike" class="headerlink" title="3. Personal selling: First can build up the brand recognition and product awareness of Yadea Y1S, then stimulate the customer’s demand by building a relationship at the same time persuading and providing technical information about the electric motorbike."></a>3. Personal selling: First can build up the brand recognition and product awareness of Yadea Y1S, then stimulate the customer’s demand by building a relationship at the same time persuading and providing technical information about the electric motorbike.</h5><h5 id="4-Other-promotional-methods-i-brand-promotion-advertising-and-marketing-ii-expansion-of-the-distributor-points-of-sales-overhaul-campaign-iii-expansion-of-the-international-sales-iv-development-of-the-online-platform-including-online-sales-promotion-and-marketing"><a href="#4-Other-promotional-methods-i-brand-promotion-advertising-and-marketing-ii-expansion-of-the-distributor-points-of-sales-overhaul-campaign-iii-expansion-of-the-international-sales-iv-development-of-the-online-platform-including-online-sales-promotion-and-marketing" class="headerlink" title="4. Other promotional methods: (i) brand promotion, advertising, and marketing; (ii) expansion of the distributor points of sales overhaul campaign; (iii) expansion of the international sales; (iv) development of the online platform, including online sales promotion and marketing;"></a>4. Other promotional methods: (i) brand promotion, advertising, and marketing; (ii) expansion of the distributor points of sales overhaul campaign; (iii) expansion of the international sales; (iv) development of the online platform, including online sales promotion and marketing;</h5><hr><p>[<a href="#_ftnref1">1]</a> <a href="https://www.worlddata.info/europe/united-kingdom/telecommunication.php">https://www.worlddata.info/europe/united-kingdom/telecommunication.php</a></p><p>[<a href="#_ftnref2">2]</a> <a href="https://finbox.com/OTCPK:YADG.F/explorer/total_rev">https://finbox.com/OTCPK:YADG.F/explorer/total_rev</a> </p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>Marketing</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>The UK&#39;s Economic</title>
    <link href="/2022/10/17/The_UKs_economic_Situation/"/>
    <url>/2022/10/17/The_UKs_economic_Situation/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="K-International-trade-statistics"><a href="#K-International-trade-statistics" class="headerlink" title="K: International trade statistics"></a>K: International trade statistics</h3><h4 id="1-Major-export"><a href="#1-Major-export" class="headerlink" title="1. Major export:"></a>1. Major export:</h4><p>From the data, we can see a growing trend in the export of goods and services from the year 2016 to 2019. There was an apparent shrinking in 2020 due to the outbreak of Covid-19. The global ranking of the UK in 2021 of exports in goods and services ranked 7th. The value of the UK’s total trade in the 12 months to the end of July 2022 is £1,441.9 billion, and the UK possesses £676.6 billion in export and £765.3billion in imports. Total exports of goods in July 2022 increased by £2.1 billion (6.7%), driven by a £1.3 billion (7.9%) increase in exports to EU countries, while exports to non-EU countries increased by £0.8 billion (5.4%)(Statistics, September 2022). The increase in exports to EU countries in 2022 was primarily driven by higher exports of fuels, machinery and transport equipment. The left table shows the top 5 UK exports of goods from 12 months to the end of July 2022. The right table is the top 5 UK services exports for four quarters to the end of March 2022(Statistics, October 2022). The UK’s top 5 trading partners for goods exports in 2021 are the United States, Germany, Netherlands, Ireland, and France. </p><table><thead><tr><th><strong>Top</strong>   <strong>5</strong> <strong>UK goods   exports</strong></th><th><strong>Value   (£ billion)</strong></th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>Mechanical  power generators</td><td>24.7</td></tr><tr><td>Crude  oil</td><td>24.7</td></tr><tr><td>Medicinal  and pharmaceutical products</td><td>23.1</td></tr><tr><td>Cars</td><td>21.8</td></tr><tr><td>Non-ferrous  metals</td><td>17.2</td></tr></tbody></table><table><thead><tr><th><strong>Top   5 UK services exports</strong></th><th><strong>Value   (£ billion)</strong></th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>Other  business services</td><td>126.8</td></tr><tr><td>Financial  services</td><td>61.3</td></tr><tr><td>Telecomms,  computer and information</td><td>31.0</td></tr><tr><td>Insurance  and pension services</td><td>21.9</td></tr><tr><td>Transport  services</td><td>19.2</td></tr></tbody></table><h4 id="2-Major-Imports"><a href="#2-Major-Imports" class="headerlink" title="2. Major Imports:"></a>2. Major Imports:</h4><p>There was a growing value of capital in goods and services from 2016 to 2019, and in 2020, there was a massive decline in imports of goods compared with services. The global ranking of 2021 of imported goods and services ranked 6th in the UK. Total imports of goods decreased by £0.5 billion (0.9%) in July 2022 because of a £0.4 billion (1.5%) fall in imports from non-EU countries, while imports from EU countries decreased by £0.1 billion (0.3%). Imports from non-EU countries were higher than imports from the EU due to the significant increases in the imports of fuels in the last months of 2021. The left table shows the top 5 UK goods imports from 12 months to the end of July 2022. The right table is the top 5 UK services imports for four quarters to the end of March 2022. The UK’s top 5 trading partners for imports of goods in 2021 are China, Germany, the United States, the Netherlands, and Norway. </p><table><thead><tr><th><strong>Top</strong> <strong>5</strong> <strong>UK goods   imports</strong></th><th><strong>Value (£   billion)</strong></th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>Gas</td><td>39.9</td></tr><tr><td>Cars</td><td>32.8</td></tr><tr><td>Medicinal and  pharmaceutical products</td><td>28.1</td></tr><tr><td>Crude oil</td><td>28.0</td></tr><tr><td>Refined oil</td><td>22.7</td></tr></tbody></table><table><thead><tr><th><strong>Top 5 UK services imports</strong></th><th><strong>Value (£   billion)</strong></th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>Other business  services</td><td>79.9</td></tr><tr><td>Transport  services</td><td>23.3</td></tr><tr><td>Travel services</td><td>19.6</td></tr><tr><td>Financial  services</td><td>16.9</td></tr><tr><td>Intellectual  property services</td><td>12.8</td></tr></tbody></table><h4 id="3-Balance-of-payment-situation"><a href="#3-Balance-of-payment-situation" class="headerlink" title="3. Balance of payment situation:"></a>3. Balance of payment situation:</h4><p>The balance of payments is the record of all international financial transactions made by a country’s residents, including the current account, the capital account, and the financial account. All trades conducted by private and public sectors are accounted for in the BOP to determine how much money is going in and out of a country. The data published by the International Monetary Fund has shown the BOP of the current account balance from the year 1970 to 2021(Bank, 2022). From 1997 till now, the UK has been in a current account deficit condition. The current account deficit is a measurement of a country’s trade where the value of the goods and services it imports exceeds the value of the products it exports.</p><h4 id="4-Exchange-rates"><a href="#4-Exchange-rates" class="headerlink" title="4. Exchange rates"></a>4. Exchange rates</h4><p>The UK is a floating exchange rate regime in which the price of a country’s currency is determined by the foreign exchange markets. It is based on the supply and demand of one currency relative to another. The United Kingdom entered the floating exchange rate regime in 1972, along with most other countries in the world, leaving the Bretton Woods system behind. The current rate of exchange on October 18th of the British Pound to the Chinese Yuan is 8.165. And the overall exchange rate for the past year has declined from around 8.8 in October 2021 to 8.1 in October 2022(Barchart, 2022).     </p><p><img src="/img/eco-1.jpeg" alt="eco-1"></p><h3 id="L-Trade-Restriction"><a href="#L-Trade-Restriction" class="headerlink" title="L: Trade Restriction"></a>L: Trade Restriction</h3><h4 id="1-Embargoes"><a href="#1-Embargoes" class="headerlink" title="1. Embargoes:"></a>1. Embargoes:</h4><p>There are 38 trade barriers from the UK to China for example sectors like food and drink, healthcare services, pharmaceuticals and biotechnology etc. In the food and drink sector, the UK has not permitted cherries, lamb meat, and hops to export to China(Government.UK, 2020). There is also a partial arms embargo on China, and the military items covered by the embargo are lethal weapons Field(Government.UK, December, 2020) such as machine guns, large-caliber weapons, bombs, torpedoes, rockets and missiles. </p><h4 id="2-Quotas"><a href="#2-Quotas" class="headerlink" title="2. Quotas:"></a>2. Quotas:</h4><p>We can look at the UK tariff rate quotas for 2022. In the commodity part, there is poultry, pigment, cereals, olive oil, rice, beef, garlic, sugar, milk products, and eggs(Government.UK, 2022b). There is an order number and annual quantity available for each order, and it can be divided into 4 sub-periods of the available quantity. For more information visit the website of the UK trade quotas(Government.UK, 2022c).</p><h4 id="3-Import-taxes"><a href="#3-Import-taxes" class="headerlink" title="3. Import taxes:"></a>3. Import taxes:</h4><p>UK import tax will vary depending on several factors, including the type of item sent, the value, the country of origin, and the intended use including personal or commercial. You pay VAT when you buy the goods or to the delivery company before you receive them. VAT is not charged on goods that are gifts worth £39 or less. If you have to pay VAT to the delivery company, it’s charged on the total package value, including the value of the goods postage, packaging and insurance, and any duty you owe. You will need to pay VAT to the delivery company if the goods are gifts sent to you by someone else and worth more than £39 and the excise goods(Government.UK, 2022a).</p><h4 id="4-Tariffs"><a href="#4-Tariffs" class="headerlink" title="4. Tariffs:"></a>4. Tariffs:</h4><p>The UK Global Tariff (UKGT) is the UK’s first independent tariff policy which replaced the EU Common External Tariff (CET) which applied until 31 December 2020. This tariff entered into force on 1 January 2021. The Government has published the UK Global Tariff (UKGT) which applies to all goods imported unless:</p><ul><li>the country imports come from has a preferential <a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/collections/the-uks-trade-agreements">trade agreement</a></li><li>an exception applies, such as a relief or <a href="https://www.gov.uk/guidance/duty-suspensions-and-tariff-quotas">tariff suspension</a></li><li>the goods come from developing countries covered by the <a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/trading-with-developing-nations">Generalised Scheme of Preferences</a></li></ul><h4 id="5-Licensing"><a href="#5-Licensing" class="headerlink" title="5. Licensing:"></a>5. Licensing:</h4><p>The UK Government Licensing Framework (UKGLF) provides a policy and legal overview of the arrangements for licensing the use and re-use of public sector information both in the central government and the wider public sector. It sets out best practices and standardizes licensing principles. In the context of the UKGLF, the licenses ensure that users are aware of the need to use the information responsibly and not in ways that mislead others. The UKGLF provides a coherent standard approach to licensing through a portfolio of licensing solutions developed to cover the following situations field (Archives, 2016).</p><ul><li><p>Free use and re-use for all purposes both commercial and non-commercial-the Open Government Licence</p></li><li><p>Free use and re-use for non-commercial purposes only-the Non-Commercial Government Licence</p></li><li><p>Where charges are made for the re-use of information, including in the context of s102 of the Protection of Freedoms Act 20121 and under the Re-use of Public Sector Information Regulations 2015-the Charged Licence </p></li></ul><h4 id="6-Customs-duties"><a href="#6-Customs-duties" class="headerlink" title="6. Customs duties:"></a>6. Customs duties:</h4><p>You’ll be charged Customs Duty on all goods sent from outside the UK (or the UK and the EU if you’re in Northern Ireland) if they’re either excise goods or worth more than £135. If you’re charged Customs Duty, you’ll need to pay it on both the price paid for the goods; postage, packaging, and insurance. In the UK you pay Customs Duty on excise goods of any value</p><table><thead><tr><th>Non-excise goods worth £135 or less</th><th>No charge</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>Gifts above £135  and up to £630</td><td>2.5%, but rates  are lower for some goods</td></tr><tr><td>Gifts above £630  and other goods above £135</td><td>The rate depends  on the type of goods and where they came from</td></tr></tbody></table><h3 id="M-Extent-of-economic-activity-not-included-in-cash-income-activities"><a href="#M-Extent-of-economic-activity-not-included-in-cash-income-activities" class="headerlink" title="M: Extent of economic activity not included in cash income activities"></a>M: Extent of economic activity not included in cash income activities</h3><h4 id="1-Countertrades"><a href="#1-Countertrades" class="headerlink" title="1. Countertrades:"></a>1. Countertrades:</h4><p>Many governments reduce imbalances in trade between countries using a countertrade system of international trading. Companies that consider countertrade typically want to expand into a foreign market, increase sales, build customer and supplier relationships, and overcome liquidity challenges. This type of international trade is more common in developing countries with limited foreign exchange or credit facilities. </p><p>Countertrade can be classified into three broad categories: barter, counterpurchase, and offset. Bartering is the oldest countertrade arrangement. It is the direct exchange of goods and services with an equivalent value but with no cash settlement. For example, a bag of nuts might be exchanged for coffee beans or meat. Under a counterpurchase arrangement, the exporter sells goods or services to an importer and agrees to also purchase other goods from the importer within a specified period. The exporters entering into a counterpurchase arrangement must use a trading firm to sell the goods they purchase and will not use the goods themselves. In an offset arrangement, the seller assists in marketing products manufactured by the buying country or allows part of the exported product’s assembly to be carried out by manufacturers in the buying country. This practice is common in aerospace, defense and certain infrastructure industries.</p><h4 id="2-Foreign-aid-received"><a href="#2-Foreign-aid-received" class="headerlink" title="2. Foreign aid received:"></a>2. Foreign aid received:</h4><p>The UK’s trading relationships with developing countries positively impact UK consumers by providing a wider choice of everyday goods at lower costs, making household incomes go further. For UK businesses, imports from developing countries support UK exports. For example, according to UN Comtrade data, in 2016, 48% of UK imports of un-processed tea came from Kenya, 10% of imports of prepared fish came from Ghana, and 21% of T-shirts came from Bangladesh. By helping developing countries trade more with the UK and the rest of the world, the UK can support their economic development which helps drive growth and jobs in a way that aid-spending alone cannot (Lee, 2018). </p><h3 id="N-Labor-force"><a href="#N-Labor-force" class="headerlink" title="N: Labor force"></a>N: Labor force</h3><h4 id="1-Size"><a href="#1-Size" class="headerlink" title="1. Size:"></a>1. Size:</h4><p>The employment rate has decreased since the start of the coronavirus pandemic, and it increased at the end of 2020. However, the employment rate decreased from June to August 2022, and self-employed workers increased. Compared with the previous three-month period from March to May 2022 which had a higher employment rate than other recent periods(Statistics, 2022). </p><p><img src="/img/eco2.jpeg" alt="eco2"></p><h4 id="2-Unemployment-rates"><a href="#2-Unemployment-rates" class="headerlink" title="2. Unemployment rates:"></a>2. Unemployment rates:</h4><p>The unemployment rate had generally been falling since late 2013 until the start of the COVID-19 pandemic. It increased until the end of 2020 but has now returned to pre-coronavirus pandemic levels. Over the latest three-month period, the unemployment rate decreased to the lowest rate of around 3.5%.</p><p><img src="/img/eco3.jpeg" alt="eco3"></p><h3 id="O-Inflation-rates"><a href="#O-Inflation-rates" class="headerlink" title="O: Inflation rates:"></a>O: Inflation rates:</h3><p>The inflation rate in the United Kingdom was 10.1 percent in September 2022, compared with 9.9 percent in August 2022. This is the joint-highest inflation rate recorded for the Consumer Price Index (CPI) in the UK, with prices also rising by 10.1 percent a few weeks earlier in July 2022 (Statistica, 2022). During the most recent month, housing costs, such as energy and water, had the most significant price increases. </p><p><img src="/img/eco4.jpeg" alt="eco4"></p><p>Reference:</p><p>Archives, N. (2016). UK government Licensing Framework. <a href="https://cdn.nationalarchives.gov.uk/documents/information-management/uk-government-licensing-framework.pdf">https://cdn.nationalarchives.gov.uk/documents/information-management/uk-government-licensing-framework.pdf</a> </p><p>Bank, T. W. (2022). <em>Current account balance (BoP, current US$) - United Kingdom</em>. <a href="https://data.worldbank.org/indicator/BN.CAB.XOKA.CD?end=2021&amp;locations=GB&amp;start=1970">https://data.worldbank.org/indicator/BN.CAB.XOKA.CD?end=2021&amp;locations=GB&amp;start=1970</a></p><p>Barchart. (2022). <em>British Pound to Chinese Yuan</em> <a href="https://www.barchart.com/forex/quotes/^GBPCNY/overview">https://www.barchart.com/forex/quotes/%5EGBPCNY/overview</a></p><p>Government.UK. (2020). <em>Trade barriers in China</em>. <a href="https://www.check-international-trade-barriers.service.gov.uk/barriers/?resolved=0&amp;location=cn">https://www.check-international-trade-barriers.service.gov.uk/barriers/?resolved=0&amp;location=cn</a></p><p>Government.UK. (2022a). <em>Tax and customs for goods sent from abroad</em>. <a href="https://www.gov.uk/goods-sent-from-abroad/tax-and-duty">https://www.gov.uk/goods-sent-from-abroad/tax-and-duty</a></p><p>Government.UK. (2022b). <em>UK tariff rate quotas 2022</em>. <a href="https://www.gov.uk/guidance/uk-tariff-rate-quotas-2022">https://www.gov.uk/guidance/uk-tariff-rate-quotas-2022</a></p><p>Government.UK. (2022c). UK trade quotas. <a href="https://data.api.trade.gov.uk/v1/datasets/uk-trade-quotas/versions/v1.0.22/metadata?format=html">https://data.api.trade.gov.uk/v1/datasets/uk-trade-quotas/versions/v1.0.22/metadata?format=html</a> </p><p>Government.UK. (December, 2020). <em>UK arms embargo on mainland China and Hong Kong</em>. <a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/collections/uk-arms-embargo-on-mainland-china-and-hong-kong">https://www.gov.uk/government/collections/uk-arms-embargo-on-mainland-china-and-hong-kong</a></p><p>Lee, J. (2018). <em>Aid and trade</em>. <a href="https://una.org.uk/magazine/2018-1/aid-and-trade">https://una.org.uk/magazine/2018-1/aid-and-trade</a></p><p>Statistica. (2022). <em>Inflation rate for the Consumer Price Index (CPI) in the United Kingdom from January 1989 to September 2022</em>. <a href="https://www.statista.com/statistics/306648/inflation-rate-consumer-price-index-cpi-united-kingdom-uk/">https://www.statista.com/statistics/306648/inflation-rate-consumer-price-index-cpi-united-kingdom-uk/</a></p><p>Statistics, N. (2022). <em>Employment in the UK: October 2022</em>. <a href="https://www.ons.gov.uk/employmentandlabourmarket/peopleinwork/employmentandemployeetypes/bulletins/employmentintheuk/latest">https://www.ons.gov.uk/employmentandlabourmarket/peopleinwork/employmentandemployeetypes/bulletins/employmentintheuk/latest</a></p><p>Statistics, N. (September 2022). <em>UK trade: July 2022</em>. <a href="https://www.ons.gov.uk/economy/nationalaccounts/balanceofpayments/bulletins/uktrade/july2022">https://www.ons.gov.uk/economy/nationalaccounts/balanceofpayments/bulletins/uktrade/july2022</a></p><p>Statistics, O. (October 2022). <em>UK trade in numbers</em> <a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/statistics/uk-trade-in-numbers/uk-trade-in-numbers-web-version#import-statistics">https://www.gov.uk/government/statistics/uk-trade-in-numbers/uk-trade-in-numbers-web-version#import-statistics</a> </p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>Trade</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Uk&#39;s Political system</title>
    <link href="/2022/09/23/UK_political_system/"/>
    <url>/2022/09/23/UK_political_system/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><u>Summary:</u> </p><p>The British political system is a two-party system and in order to measure a country’s political stability, we can look at the indicator of the political stability index. The latest data from 2020 shows that the UK scores 0.47 which proves that the UK has a relatively stable government compared with the average level in the world. The 2022 International IP shows the UK has ranked No.2 out of the 55 economies which indicates that the UK has a mature law and supervision system to continue to promote and develop the intellectual property market. The fundamental principles of business culture in the United Kingdom are courtesy, politeness, discipline, and punctuality and most British businesspeople are following a rational and pragmatic approach.</p><p><strong>C: Political system</strong></p><p><strong>Political structure:</strong> Britain is a constitutional monarchy governed by a king or a queen and it is also a parliamentary democracy whose government is controlled by a parliament that has been elected by the people. The highest positions in the government are filled by the members of the directly elected parliament.</p><p><strong>Political parties:</strong> The British political system is a two-party system. Since the 1920s, the two dominant parties have been the Conservative Party and the Labour Party. In September of 2022, Liz Truss became the new prime minister of the UK after meeting the queen at Balmoral. Her first significant act as prime minister is to deal with the high price of energy and made it affordable to the people of the UK. </p><p>Stability of the government: To measure a country’s political stability, we can look at the indicator of the political stability index. It ranges in degree from -2.5 meaning unstable to +2.5 which means stable. The given data shows from the year 1996 to 2020, the average value for the United Kingdom was 0.48. With a minimum of 0.08 points in 2018 and a maximum of 1.04 points in 2000. In the latest data from 2020, the world average value based on 194 countries is -0.07, and the UK scores 0.47 (Bank, 2020).  The compared result proves that the UK has a relatively stable government with better performance than the average level in the world. A general conclusion can be obtained through this observation from the British government. The stable political environment is of great opportunity to expand our market in this country.</p><p><strong>Special taxes in the UK:</strong></p><p>In 2021/22, the UK government raised over £915 billion a year in receipts – income from taxes and other sources. This is equivalent to around 39% of the size of the UK economy, as measured by GDP. In cash terms, the hardest hit tax in 2020/21 was VAT, where receipts were over £17 billion lower, compared with 2019/20. Consumers were less able to go out and spend during the pandemic, and Government policies, such as cutting VAT from 20% to 5% for the ‘hospitality, accommodation, and attractions sector, have also affected VAT receipt (Matthew, 2022).  </p><p>For example, the carbon tax. A Carbon tax aims to make individuals and firms pay the full social cost of carbon pollution. This special tax will encourage individuals to reduce pollution and encourage them to use more environmentally products such as solar power. It also makes polluters pay the external cost of carbon emissions. In contrast, there exist some problems, for example, enterprises may avoid paying carbon tax by secretly polluting the greenhouse gases in the environment (Pettinger, 2020 ). Under this scenario, the government should strengthen education on ethical behavior and set guidelines and regulations for the people to follow.</p><p><strong>Local government:</strong> Normally, Government is responsible for deciding how the country is run, they set taxes, and deciding how to best deliver public services such as the National Health Service, and welfare benefits such as the state pension. In the United Kingdom, Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland have their devolved governments and each with varying powers. The parliament’s job is to look closely at the Government’s plans and to monitor the way they are running things, they work on behalf of the government’s decision by examining new proposals closely and suggesting improvements, checking how public money is being spent, and tracking how new laws are working out in practice (Parliament, 2022). </p><p><strong>D: Legal system</strong></p><p><strong>Judiciary system:</strong> The UK does not have a constitution that is contained in a written constitutional instrument. It is to be found in the statutes passed by Parliament and in the common law, which developed over historical reasons. As a state made up of several separate jurisdictions, the United Kingdom does not have a single unified legal system. The UK lacks a written constitution on the current political and legal institutions, also their institutions did not separate the functions and powers of the three different branches of the state which are the executive, the legislature, and the judiciary (Judiciary, 2022). </p><p>For example, the government is made up of MPs and peers who are also members of the legislature including the House of Commons and the House of Lords. The UK public elects 650 Members of Parliament to represent their interests and concerns in the House of Commons. The House of Lords is the second chamber of the UK Parliament. It plays a crucial role in examining bills, questioning government action, and investigating public policy. In this case, it is usually quite intricate and requires some time to make a unified decision or pass through the law such as the Brexit issue. If a company wants to do business in the UK it would be better to choose a time after the factionalism.</p><p><strong>Intellectual property</strong>: IP usually gives the creator an exclusive right over the use of his creation for a certain period. Copyright, patents, designs, and trademarks are common rights for intellectual property protection. 179 countries have signed up to the Berne Convention which lays down a common framework and agreement between nations concerning intellectual property rights. The 2022 International IP Index published by the US Chamber of Commerce has given out the rankings and the indicators of the overall score of IP. The UK has ranked No.2 out of the 55 economies. It has a high ranking in the sector of copyright and trademark and a relatively lower ranking in the patents and design rights (commerce, 2022). Copyright law originated in the United Kingdom from a concept of common law which is the Statute of Anne 1709. It became statutory with the passing of the Copyright Act of 1911. The current act is the Copyright, Designs, and Patents Act 1988(service, 2022). The UK has a mature law and supervision system to continue to promote and develop the intellectual property market. </p><p><strong>E: Social Organization</strong></p><p><strong>Group behavior:</strong> Social organization refers to the network of relationships in a group and how they interconnect with each other. For example, Social Value UK is a Joint Member Network of Social Value International, the global standard-setting organization for social value and impact management. Social Value International has also partnered with the UNDP and SDG Impact to support the adoption of the SDG Impact Standards globally. Social Value UK’s mission is to change the way society accounts for value through principles, practice, people, and power and develop guidance, tools, and support to help achieve the principles. Businesses can make a cooperation with these organizations and achieve common goals to enhance customers’ favorability and their reputation. </p><p><strong>The UK social classes:</strong> </p><p>Approximated Social Grade with its six categories A, B, C1, C2, D, and E is a socio-economic classification produced by the ONS (UK Office for National Statistics) by applying an algorithm developed by members of the MRS Census &amp; Geodemographics Group. It applies to every Household Reference Person (HRP) aged 16 to 64 (Geographics, 2014). </p><table><thead><tr><th>Social Grade</th><th>Description</th><th>% HRP population (UK)</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>AB</td><td>Higher &amp; intermediate managerial,  administrative, professional occupations</td><td>22.17</td></tr><tr><td>C1</td><td>Supervisory, clerical &amp; junior managerial,  administrative, professional occupations</td><td>30.84</td></tr><tr><td>C2</td><td>Skilled manual occupations</td><td>20.94</td></tr><tr><td>DE</td><td>Semi-skilled &amp; unskilled manual occupations,  Unemployed and lowest grade occupations</td><td>26.05</td></tr></tbody></table><p>From the data in the table, we can tell more than half of the proportion of people in the UK are in the middle class and above. It is clear for the company to target its customer to a specific group of social classes.</p><p><strong>Clubs:</strong> The Equality Act 2010 brings together harmonizes, in some respects extends previous equality laws. It aims to make it more consistent, clearer, and easier to follow, to make society fairer. The Act protects people from discrimination based on protected characteristics. Examples of associations include private clubs such as golf and other sports clubs, ex-forces clubs, alumni clubs, social clubs, working men’s clubs, gaming clubs, and drinking clubs. Some charities also meet the definition of an association, for example, the Scout Association and Girlguiding UK. Such charities are also subject to additional provisions relating to the provision of charitable benefits.</p><p><strong>Subcultures:</strong> Since 2001, the foreign-born share of the population has doubled to about nine million. Meanwhile, the number of those from an ethnic minority background, including ‘White Other’, has more than doubled to over 13 million, their share of the population rising from 10% to 21%. Just over one-third of all births now involve at least one foreign-born parent and one in three pupils in English state-funded schools are from an ethnic minority background. The (UK, 2021) Gaming and non-mainstream religious groups are the two leading subcultures in the UK today, according to research that highlights the value to marketers of tapping into niche cultural groups. (WARC, 2020) Overall, 73% connect with subcultures virtually. And of those online-only connectors, two-thirds are younger (67% are under 44) and are more likely to connect to gaming, body modification, fandom, and influencer subcultures. YouTube is the main platform for contact (38%) and Facebook communities remain at the heart of subculture involvement. Understanding the subcultures can be useful for the business to understand and better adapt to the local market.</p><p><strong>F: Business customs and practices</strong></p><p>The fundamental principles of business culture in the United Kingdom are courtesy, politeness, discipline, and punctuality. Most British businesspeople are following a rational and pragmatic approach. Only on rare occasions, a commitment is announced right away, while agreements need to be formalized in writing. Due to the high frequency of meetings, people working in an office environment are often away from their desks. (Expatica, 2022) This accounts for the comparatively high number of memos sent and received in a UK company. So, we need to arrange appointments in advance. Dress codes in the UK are still comparatively strict. Colleagues appreciate a sense of fashion and quality. While men wear suits, ties, and striped or colored shirts and black shoes while women wear suits with trousers or skirts or normally in dresses, often with high heels. In most companies, colleagues enjoy an after-work drink together on a Friday night. Apart from this custom, the tendency is to keep work and private life strictly separated. Invitations to someone’s private home are gestures of affection and sympathy, which is uncommon between mere business partners. Colleagues exchange business cards before or at the beginning of a meeting. A card usually displays someone’s job title, first and surname. Academic titles are not necessarily on a business card unless they are relevant to your work. It is essentially important to understand its local customs when doing business with the British people. </p><p><strong>Reference:</strong></p><p>Bank, T. W. (2020). <em>United Kingdom: Political stability</em>. <a href="https://www.theglobaleconomy.com/United-Kingdom/wb_political_stability/">https://www.theglobaleconomy.com/United-Kingdom/wb_political_stability/</a></p><p>commerce, U. c. o. (2022). <em>International IP Index</em>. <a href="https://www.uschamber.com/assets/documents/IPIndex-FullReport_2022.pdf.pdf#asset:185047@1">https://www.uschamber.com/assets/documents/IPIndex-FullReport_2022.pdf.pdf#asset:185047@1</a></p><p>Expatica. (2022). <em>Business culture in the United Kingdom</em>. <a href="https://www.expatica.com/uk/working/employment-basics/uk-business-culture-103182/?__cf_chl_tk=N8dWYGcvfYKJg1HMN3Ge6rUGR_mAA.p6eRTck0ccB3U-1664037962-0-gaNycGzNDGU">https://www.expatica.com/uk/working/employment-basics/uk-business-culture-103182/?__cf_chl_tk=N8dWYGcvfYKJg1HMN3Ge6rUGR_mAA.p6eRTck0ccB3U-1664037962-0-gaNycGzNDGU</a></p><p>Geographics, U. (2014). <em>Social Grade</em>. <a href="https://www.ukgeographics.co.uk/blog/social-grade-a-b-c1-c2-d-e">https://www.ukgeographics.co.uk/blog/social-grade-a-b-c1-c2-d-e</a></p><p>Judiciary. (2022). The justice system and the constitution. <a href="https://www.judiciary.uk/about-the-judiciary/our-justice-system/jud-acc-ind/justice-sys-and-constitution/">https://www.judiciary.uk/about-the-judiciary/our-justice-system/jud-acc-ind/justice-sys-and-constitution/</a> </p><p>Matthew. (2022). <em>Tax statistics: an overview</em>. <a href="https://researchbriefings.files.parliament.uk/documents/CBP-8513/CBP-8513.pdf">https://researchbriefings.files.parliament.uk/documents/CBP-8513/CBP-8513.pdf</a></p><p>Parliament, U. (2022). <em>Parliament and the Government</em>. <a href="https://www.parliament.uk/about/how/role/relations-with-other-institutions/parliament-government/">https://www.parliament.uk/about/how/role/relations-with-other-institutions/parliament-government/</a></p><p>Pettinger, T. (2020 ). <em>Carbon Tax – Pros and Cons</em>. <a href="https://www.economicshelp.org/blog/2207/economics/carbon-tax-pros-and-cons/">https://www.economicshelp.org/blog/2207/economics/carbon-tax-pros-and-cons/</a></p><p>service, U. c. r. (2022). <em>UK Copyright Law</em>. <a href="https://copyrightservice.co.uk/copyright/p01_uk_copyright_law">https://copyrightservice.co.uk/copyright/p01_uk_copyright_law</a></p><p>UK, M. W. (2021). <em>Impact of immigration in changing the UK population</em>. <a href="https://www.migrationwatchuk.org/briefing-paper/492/impact-of-immigration-in-changing-the-uk-population">https://www.migrationwatchuk.org/briefing-paper/492/impact-of-immigration-in-changing-the-uk-population</a></p><p>WARC. (2020). <em>UK subcultures are alive and well</em>. <a href="https://www.warc.com/newsandopinion/news/uk-subcultures-are-alive-and-well/en-gb/43997">https://www.warc.com/newsandopinion/news/uk-subcultures-are-alive-and-well/en-gb/43997</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>Politics</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Hello, my distinguished guest</title>
    <link href="/2022/09/23/hello/"/>
    <url>/2022/09/23/hello/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hi 👋, I am Diana Zhang</p><p>Welcome to my blog :)</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>Misc</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
</search>
