<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<search>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>To 🐝 or not to 🐝</title>
    <link href="/2022/09/23/UK_political_system/"/>
    <url>/2022/09/23/UK_political_system/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Britain is a constitutional monarchy governed by a king or a queen and It is also a parliamentary democracy. whose government is controlled by a parliament that has been elected by the people. The highest positions in the government are filled by the members of the directly elected parliament.</p><p>  The British political system is a two-party system. Since the 1920s, the two dominant parties have been the Conservative Party and the Labour Party. In September of 2022, Liz Truss became the new prime minister of UK after meeting the queen at Balmoral. Her first significant act as prime minister is to deal with the high price of energy and made it affordable to the people of UK. </p><p>For the political stability we can look at the indicator of the political stability index which ranges from -2.5 (weak)to +2.5(strong). From the year 1996 to 2020, the average value for the United Kingdom was 0.48 with a minimum of 0.08 points in 2018 and a maximum of 1.04 points in 2000. The latest value from 2020 is 0.47 and compared to the world average value based on 194 countries -0.07. [<a href="#_ftn1">1]</a>Which can indicates that UK has a relatively stable government which performed better than the average level in the world. From these data we can infer to the actual situation that the British government is guiding the whole country. </p><p>As for the special taxes in UK, there are carbon tax, sugar tax and petrol tax. A Carbon tax aims to make individuals and firms pay the full social cost of carbon pollution. This special tax will encourage individuals to reduce pollution and encourage them to use more environmentally products such as solar power. It also makes polluters paying external cost of carbon emissions. In contrast there also exist some problems for example, enterprises may avoid paying carbon tax by secretly polluting the greenhouse gases into the society.[<a href="#_ftn2">2]</a> Under this scenario the government should strengthen the education on ethical behavior and set guidelines and regulations for the people to follow. Consumption of sugar imposes costs on individuals such as resulting in lower life expectancy. [<a href="#_ftn3">3]</a>By imposing sugar tax on the product can reduce the consumption of unhealthy food and guiding people living a healthier life. It also encourages firms to produce healthier food and beverages. Besides that it also helps the government to raise revenue and have a higher spending on health care sector. However increasing the tax may still cause negative effect such as tax evasion and increase the living cost of the lower income family. In terms of the petrol cost, a higher petrol tax could help improve struggling government tax revenues and also contribute to a better environment and lower congestion levels. [<a href="#_ftn4">4]</a></p><p>The Government is responsible for deciding how the country is run, they  set taxes, choose what to spend public money on and decide how best to deliver public services such as the National Health Service, welfare benefits such as the state pension and subsidies. Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland have their own devolved governments each with varying powers Parliament’s job is to look closely at the Government’s plans and to monitor the way they are running things, they work behalf on the government decision by examining new proposals closely and suggesting improvements, checking how public money is being spent and tracking how new laws are working out in practice. [<a href="#_ftn5">5]</a> </p><p>For historical reasons, as a state made up of several separate jurisdictions, the United Kingdom does not have a single unified legal system.[<a href="#_ftn6">6]</a> UK lack of a written constitution on the current political and legal institutions also their institutions did not separate the functions and powers of the three different branches of the state, the executive, the legislature, and the judiciary. [<a href="#_ftn7">7]</a> </p><p>The UK is a parliamentary democracy and a constitutional monarchy. The Parliament of the United Kingdom is sovereign. It is made up of the House of Commons, the House of Lords and the Crown. </p><hr><p>[<a href="#_ftnref1">1]</a> <a href="https://www.theglobaleconomy.com/United-Kingdom/wb_political_stability/">https://www.theglobaleconomy.com/United-Kingdom/wb_political_stability/</a></p><p>[<a href="#_ftnref2">2]</a> <a href="https://www.economicshelp.org/blog/2207/economics/carbon-tax-pros-and-cons/">https://www.economicshelp.org/blog/2207/economics/carbon-tax-pros-and-cons/</a></p><p>[<a href="#_ftnref3">3]</a> <a href="https://www.economicshelp.org/blog/14884/economics/sugar-tax-debate/">https://www.economicshelp.org/blog/14884/economics/sugar-tax-debate/</a></p><p>[<a href="#_ftnref4">4]</a> <a href="https://www.economicshelp.org/blog/14884/economics/sugar-tax-debate/">https://www.economicshelp.org/blog/14884/economics/sugar-tax-debate/</a></p><p>[<a href="#_ftnref5">5]</a> <a href="https://www.parliament.uk/about/how/role/relations-with-other-institutions/parliament-government/">https://www.parliament.uk/about/how/role/relations-with-other-institutions/parliament-government/</a></p><p>[<a href="#_ftnref6">6]</a> <a href="https://www.supremecourt.uk/about/uk-judicial-system.html">https://www.supremecourt.uk/about/uk-judicial-system.html</a></p><p>[<a href="#_ftnref7">7]</a> <a href="https://www.judiciary.uk/about-the-judiciary/our-justice-system/jud-acc-ind/justice-sys-and-constitution/">https://www.judiciary.uk/about-the-judiciary/our-justice-system/jud-acc-ind/justice-sys-and-constitution/</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>Political</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Hello my distinguished guest</title>
    <link href="/2022/09/23/hello/"/>
    <url>/2022/09/23/hello/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="Hi-👋-I-am-Diana-Zhang"><a href="#Hi-👋-I-am-Diana-Zhang" class="headerlink" title="Hi 👋, I am Diana Zhang"></a>Hi 👋, I am Diana Zhang</h1><p><img src="/img/me.jpeg" alt="me"></p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>Misc</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
</search>
