<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<search>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Can knowledge sharing through social media platforms impact the wealth management behavior of Chinese citizens?</title>
    <link href="/2023/04/12/knowledge_sharing_through_social_media_platforms/"/>
    <url>/2023/04/12/knowledge_sharing_through_social_media_platforms/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Abstract"><a href="#Abstract" class="headerlink" title="Abstract:"></a>Abstract:</h2><p><em>- <strong>Purpose</strong>: Thus the objective of this report is to discover if knowledge sharing through social media platforms impacts the wealth management behavior of Chinese citizens.</em></p><p><em>- <strong>Design/methodology/approach:</strong> A questionaire is being designed</em> <em>and b*<em>oth quantitative and qualitative methods will be used to analyze the influential factors that influence users’ behavior on social media about wealth management</em></em>.*</p><p><em>- <strong>Findings:</strong> The collected data in the questionnaires which finds out that the level of trust in the influencers is the most influential factor</em><em>.</em></p><p><em>- <strong>Originality/value:</strong> This paper will demonstrate ways of maintaining trust in the virtual community and how to enhance engagement in social media such as Dou yin</em><em>.</em></p><p><em>- <strong>Practical implications:</strong> Knowledge sharing through social media platforms will have a positive impact on wealth management behavior after acquiring knowledge from the bank customer’s manager and the financial institutions.</em></p><p><em>- <strong>Social implications:</strong> This paper aims to enhance the investment awareness of the Chinese citizens by promoting knowledge sharing about wealth management on social media such as Dou yin.</em></p><h2 id="Keywords"><a href="#Keywords" class="headerlink" title="Keywords:"></a>Keywords:</h2><p>knowledge sharing, knowledge management, communist of practice, virtual community, Influencer</p><h2 id="1-Introduction"><a href="#1-Introduction" class="headerlink" title="1    Introduction"></a>1    Introduction</h2><p>In recent decades, economic development changes the demographic structure. The process of urbanization causes residents’ income to rise. The demand for household financial management has further accelerated.[1], [2]. Nowadays many Chinese citizens choose to put their money in a bank account to avoid taking risks[3]. China’s financial markets are quite primitive compared with the financial markets in the United States and Europe. In an annual report published by the Shanghai Stock Exchange, there are 85% of daily trading comes from retail investors in contrast institutional investors only contribute 15% of the trading volume [4]. Most of the financial contributions come from retail investors in China. Thus, it is important to enhance the investment awareness of the individuals and find channels to promote knowledge sharing about financial management. Affected by the COVID-19 epidemic, online entertainment demand continues to increase driving the scale of users of audio-visual applications a further growth[5]. Social media can promote knowledge sharing to the public and over 40% of users mention that they have no issue with product placements in commercial content or even in the user-generated tutorial video[6]. So social media is an appropriate tool to share different people’s ideas and opinions and Dou yin will be the chosen platform in this report. </p><h3 id="1-1-Take-Dou-yin-as-an-example-of-knowledge-sharing"><a href="#1-1-Take-Dou-yin-as-an-example-of-knowledge-sharing" class="headerlink" title="1.1    Take Dou yin as an example of knowledge sharing"></a>1.1    Take Dou yin as an example of knowledge sharing</h3><p>Dou yin is a short-video social which is founded and operated by Byte Dance in mainland China. [7] Since 2017, the scale of users has grown rapidly. Daily active users exceed 600 million[8]. Sitting on a huge number of users also with high user frequency and long user duration. Thus, many individuals and companies will choose this platform for interaction. Besides, there are also e-commerce platforms on Dou yin. According to the geographical distribution map of Dou yin user portraits newly released by Baidu Index, it is not difficult to see that Dou yin users are still mainly young and in middle-aged groups of 20-49. Dou yin accounts for about 45% of users in the first and second-tier cities which is significantly higher than other platforms like Kuai shou in China. The total population of the first and second-tier cities is estimated at 300 million which accounts for around 21% of the total population. Users who have downloaded Dou yin are so attracted to it that they spend more than 70% of their time on this platform, and the rest is used by all other apps. So, understanding how to enhance the engagement in Dou yin during the process of knowledge sharing will be greatly important. Knowledge sharing is the process of an individual’s knowledge being converted into a form that can be understood and used by other people [9]. It is different from the traditional way of sharing knowledge in the past by texting messages or giving calls. Nowadays knowledge sharing on social media has become a prevalent phenomenon across the world due to its convenience and efficiency, especially among young people [10].</p><h2 id="2-Research-Framework"><a href="#2-Research-Framework" class="headerlink" title="2    Research Framework"></a>2    Research Framework</h2><h3 id="2-1-KM-Model"><a href="#2-1-KM-Model" class="headerlink" title="2.1    KM Model"></a>2.1    KM Model</h3><p>For the research framework, the first research model uses the SECI model[11]. It has four knowledge processes and  It can be seen as a process of understanding and transforming tacit and explicit knowledge [12]. Tacit knowledge is what people learn from their experience and reflection on the internalization of knowledge. One of its characteristics is that it is hard to articulate and replicate when disseminating it around. According to what Nonaka and Takeuchi proposed, tacit knowledge is the beliefs and intuition that could only be understood and applied by those possessing it. Explicit knowledge can be expressed in different forms such as words or numbers, and it can be stored in technology like the media[13]. </p><table><thead><tr><th></th><th></th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td></td><td><img src="file:////Users/dianazhang/Library/Group%20Containers/UBF8T346G9.Office/TemporaryItems/msohtmlclip/clip_image002.jpg" alt="Diagram  Description automatically generated"></td></tr></tbody></table><p><img src="file:////Users/dianazhang/Library/Group%20Containers/UBF8T346G9.Office/TemporaryItems/msohtmlclip/clip_image003.jpg" alt="Diagram, engineering drawing  Description automatically generated"></p><p>Figure 1: The SECI model</p><p>The process of transforming tacit to tacit knowledge is called socialization, it happens when people are interacting directly face to face. The knowledge can be learned by observing, imitating, and practicing from other people[14]. Transforming tacit to explicit knowledge needs an intermediary this is the role played by the social media platform. In social media such as Dou yin, users can acquire knowledge from the videos posted by the influencers. This is a process of Externalization. The third phase of the Knowledge management process is a combination of explicit knowledge. In this stage, people can form their community and gather around to share and exchange knowledge with each other[15]. The last phase is called internalization, which is when users absorb and understand the knowledge and can apply it.</p><h3 id="2-2-KM-Process"><a href="#2-2-KM-Process" class="headerlink" title="2.2    KM Process"></a>2.2    KM Process</h3><p>Knowledge management processes are the procedures to enable and provide the creation, spreading, and utilizing of knowledge for the benefit of the organization [16]. Thus, the company needs to have the process to achieve its target. In the knowledge management process, the Wiig knowledge management cycle helps to create knowledge and use them in problem-solving or decision-making. There are four phases which are building the knowledge, holding, pooling, and applying the knowledge in life [17]. </p><p>Figure 2: The Wiig cycle model</p><p>In the first phase of building knowledge. In Dou yin, users mainly acquire knowledge from videos posted by the KOL or from live streaming. The KOL build their knowledge from formal education and training or their personal experience. Conducting marketing research and posting frequently asked questions are ways to acquire knowledge. In the second stage, knowledge is being held in the tangible forms or individuals to recollect knowledge, accumulate, or add to present knowledge. which is known as holding knowledge.</p><p>In stage three Knowledge can be pooled through interactions. Where people of the same communist of practice will gather to share and disseminate knowledge[18]. The last stage in Wiig’s model is using knowledge. After comprehending the knowledge is it time to apply it in our lives to help us solve problems. Wiig’s life cycle doesn’t have to be continuous and carried in a specific order it can be conducted in a parallel and repeated way [19].</p><h2 id="3-Data-Collection"><a href="#3-Data-Collection" class="headerlink" title="3     Data Collection"></a>3     Data Collection</h2><h3 id="3-1-Distribution-Channel"><a href="#3-1-Distribution-Channel" class="headerlink" title="3.1    Distribution Channel"></a>3.1    Distribution Channel</h3><p>To find out if knowledge sharing through social media platform impact the wealth management behavior of Chinese citizens. A questionnaire has been designed using a professional online questionnaire survey platform called questionnaire star. After designing the questions, it is then posted to some interest groups on WeChat groups viewers can scan the QR code conveniently and fill in all the questions. Finally, we have received 103 responses in total and they are people from different age groups to reduce bias. </p><h3 id="3-2-Research-Question-and-Response"><a href="#3-2-Research-Question-and-Response" class="headerlink" title="3.2    Research Question and Response"></a>3.2    Research Question and Response</h3><p>In the questionnaire, there are 13 questions in total, and by using the Likert scale method to quantify the answer for a more objective conclusion. The questionnaire contains questions including essential personal information such as age, gender, education level, financial management capital as a percentage of total income, and ways of wealth management.</p><p>Question 1 is about the age group for who filled in the questionnaires. There are 27 people among 103 people who were born after 2000 which stands around 26%. People in this age group are students and undergraduates. While 22% of the survey sample contains people born after 1990 and most of them have begun working. This group of people is the main consumption force for society. Subsequently, people born after 1980 are around 21% and they are the main pillars of the workforce of society[20]. This age group is the main consumption group of society and can stimulate and push the development of the economy in China. People born after the 1970s accounted for 20%. They are the rational consumption age group of the elder generation of China[21]. People born after 1960 take up approximately 10% of the sample data. This group of people has a lot of spare time due to retirement from work. </p><p>Question 2 is about gender, in the sample data, there are more females (around 67%) than males (around 33%).</p><p>Question 3 is about the level of education. The largest portion of the education level is bachelor’s degrees (63 people) which takes up around 62%. Followed by specialty (13 people) which occupies around 13%. The portion of respondents in the education level of master’s and above (12 people) is around 12%, which is slightly lower than that of specialty and equal to the portion of people educated in high school and below (12%, 12 people). 3 people were given the level of education as others. This distribution of results meets the Normal Distribution.</p><p>Question 4 asks for the percentage of the investment capital as total income. The result illustrated that above half of (63 people, around 61%) respondents arranged the percentage less than 25%. While 30% of the respondents (30 people) claim that they invest more than 25% and less than half of the capital as total income. There are 6 respondents (6%) having more than 50% of their total income as a capital arrangement in investment. In addition, only 4 respondents (4%) were given a portion that was above 75%.</p><p>Question 5 collects the way of wealth management of the respondents in the aspect of bank savings, stock, bond, funds, insurance, real estate, precious metal, financial derivatives, and others. The statistics show that around 69% of the respondents (71 people) manage their capital by bank savings. Followed by investment in funds, which make up over 45% of the respondents (46 people). After that, around 26% of the respondents are having stock investments. Besides, about 23% of the respondents manage their finance by insurance. The portion of the way of wealth management in real estate is approximately 18%. 18 people considered that they are investing using the approach of exchanging real estate. In addition, around 8% of the respondents (8 people) participate in the bond exchange. The portion of financial derivates investment by the respondents is around 5%. Followed by 3 people (3%) who manage their finances by investing in precious metals. Moreover, around 16% of the respondents have other approaches to financial management.</p><p>Question 7 shows the sources and channels of investment of the respondents. Almost half of the respondents (51 people) made their decision on the investment by referencing information on social media. Followed by 37% of the respondents investing in advice from financial institutions. 32% of the respondents do research by themselves. In addition, there is the same portion of respondents who acquire investment ideas by watching financial news introduced by others (both 27%). Besides, around 25% of respondents get the investment references from their investment channel as bank customers’ managers. And nearly 20% of the respondents selected the channel of consulting with a professional investment advisor. 10.68% of respondents have other channels.</p><p>Question 8 investigates the frequency of respondents paying attention to financial management on social media. The result indicated that above half of the respondents pay attention to financial management occasionally on social media, which means that they only pay attention to that when special events happen. Besides, around 28% of the respondents pay attention to that weekly. Only 10% of the respondents pay attention to that daily. And the portion is the same as that of the respondents who never shown any interest in paying attention to financial management on social media.</p><p>Question 9 shows the level of agreement of people regards social media can help them gain effective financial knowledge. Only 7 respondents (7%) show disagreement in their answers. Another 96 respondents show more than fair agreement.</p><p>Question 10 collects the given mark from the respondents on five subjects that may influence their behavior in wealth management, namely high-quality video content, content creators, interactive community, and level of trust in influencers. The mark given shows that the most significant subject the respondents considered is the level of trust in influencers (3.48/5). Followed by high-quality video content (3.28/5). Besides, the score of content creators (3.28/5) is considered less important than the high-quality video content. The least significant is the interactive community which gets an average score of 3.03/5. The detailed information on the research questions and the collected data has all been put in the appendix at the end of the report. </p><h2 id="4-Quantitative-Analysis"><a href="#4-Quantitative-Analysis" class="headerlink" title="4    Quantitative Analysis"></a>4    Quantitative Analysis</h2><table><thead><tr><th></th><th></th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td></td><td><img src="file:////Users/dianazhang/Library/Group%20Containers/UBF8T346G9.Office/TemporaryItems/msohtmlclip/clip_image005.jpg" alt="img"></td></tr></tbody></table><p>The data collected from the survey is being exported to and analyzed by the software IBM SPSS Statistics. Both quantitative and qualitative analyses will be adopted to get the conclusion. In this section, the Pearson’s correlation of each dependent variable in the survey result with the independent variable Y, which represents the degree of using financial management sharing on social media in life, will be introduced. In addition, the iteration result by adopting the Stepwise Linear Regression and the statistical data will also be illustrated.</p><h3 id="4-1-Pearson’s-Correlation"><a href="#4-1-Pearson’s-Correlation" class="headerlink" title="4.1    Pearson’s Correlation"></a>4.1    Pearson’s Correlation</h3><p>The first and most straightforward statistical analysis method is using Pearson’s correlation. Each of the correlation coefficients r ranges from 0 to 1 for illustrating the level of positive correlations of each independent variable Xi and dependent variable Y. There is a strong positive correlation when r &gt; .7, moderate positive correlation when .7 &gt; r &gt; .3, and weak positive correlation when .3 &gt; r &gt; 0). It is ranges from -1 to 0 for negative correlations of each independent variable Xi and dependent variable Y.  There is a strong negative correlation when r &lt; -.7, moderate negative correlation when -.7 &lt; r &lt; -.3, and weak negative correlation when .3 &lt; r &lt; 0. The larger the absolute value of Pearson’s correlation, the stronger the linear association between the two variables. In our case in the study of the extent to of social media platforms influence the wealth management behavior of Chinese citizens, the independent variable Y is the degree of using financial management sharing on social media in life. The other dependent variable Xi will be considered as a predictor, and we want to reach a conclusion on which factors will have a significant impact on the independent variable Y.</p><p>Figure 3: Relationship between X and the Y variable</p><h4 id="4-1-1-Ways-of-wealth-management"><a href="#4-1-1-Ways-of-wealth-management" class="headerlink" title="4.1.1   Ways of wealth management"></a>4.1.1   Ways of wealth management</h4><p>The purple circled line represents different ways of wealth management in the picture. There is a positive correlation between people managing their wealth through stock and insurance when using financial knowledge on social media in life. In contrast, there are negative correlations between bank deposits, funds, and derivatives when acquiring financial knowledge shared from social media in life. This means that people tend to listen to knowledge-sharing topics about stock and insurance compared with other ways of wealth management on social media. </p><h4 id="4-1-2-Channels-of-acquiring-financial-knowledge"><a href="#4-1-2-Channels-of-acquiring-financial-knowledge" class="headerlink" title="4.1.2   Channels of acquiring financial knowledge"></a>4.1.2   Channels of acquiring financial knowledge</h4><p>The red circled line is different channels of acquiring financial knowledge. Exceeding the expectations, people acquiring knowledge directly from social media will have a negative impact (r = -.266) on using financial knowledge in life. However, people who acquire financial management advice from financial institutions and bank customer managers would have a positive effect on using financial management advice shared on social media in life. This result illustrates that people are more willing to use the financial knowledge advice shared on social media after acquiring financial knowledge from financial institutions and bank customer managers. Thus, we can focus on pushing the content of financial knowledge sharing toward the group of people who acquire financial management advice from financial institutions and bank customer managers.</p><h4 id="4-1-3-Frequency-and-level-of-agreement"><a href="#4-1-3-Frequency-and-level-of-agreement" class="headerlink" title="4.1.3   Frequency and level of agreement"></a>4.1.3   Frequency and level of agreement</h4><p>The green line is about the frequency and level of agreement on social media. The frequency on social media means how frequently people are paying attention to financial management on social media. Due to the initial questions set in the questionnaire, one of the dependent variables X represents frequency is being designed as 1 point stands for daily and 4 points stand for never which is in the descending order that is opposite from the ordinary setting which is from never to daily. </p><p><img src="file:////Users/dianazhang/Library/Group%20Containers/UBF8T346G9.Office/TemporaryItems/msohtmlclip/clip_image007.jpg" alt="Text  Description automatically generated"></p><p>Figure 4: Opposite frequency setting</p><p> Hence, the interpretable frequency is positively correlated and the correlation coefficient in reverse (ascending) order of degree of frequency is +0.115, which indicates that the frequency of using social media has a positive effect on using financial knowledge in life. It can be interpreted as the more frequent use of social media the more it can affect the behavior of acquiring financial knowledge on social media.</p><p>The level of agreement on social media means the level of the agreement of gaining effective financial knowledge on social media. The value shows 0.648 which means that the level of the agreement of gaining effective financial knowledge will have a positive impact on acquiring financial knowledge on social media. </p><h4 id="4-1-4-Influenced-factors-on-social-media"><a href="#4-1-4-Influenced-factors-on-social-media" class="headerlink" title="4.1.4   Influenced factors on social media"></a>4.1.4   Influenced factors on social media</h4><p>The yellow circled line is the four factors which are High-quality video content, content creator (KOL), interactive community, and level of trust in influencers. These four factors all positively impact the level of using financial knowledge advice on social media in life. Among all high-quality video content and the level of trust in influencers are the two factors and their correlation coefficient are separately 0.637 and 0.633. Both possess a relatively stronger positive relationship with the Y variable of acquiring financial knowledge on social media.</p><h2 id="4-2-Stepwise-Linear-Regression"><a href="#4-2-Stepwise-Linear-Regression" class="headerlink" title="4.2    Stepwise Linear Regression"></a>4.2    Stepwise Linear Regression</h2><p><img src="file:////Users/dianazhang/Library/Group%20Containers/UBF8T346G9.Office/TemporaryItems/msohtmlclip/clip_image009.jpg" alt="Table  Description automatically generated"><br> The stepwise regression model involves adding or removing potential x variables referencing a specific threshold in succession and testing for statistical significance (p-value). </p><p>Figure 5: Stepwise Regression Model</p><p>R in a multiple regression analysis is called the coefficient of multiple correlations and shows the relationship between an independent variable and the other dependent variables in a specific model. It ranges from 0 to +1. In the first Model, there is a positive correlation between the level of agreement in gaining effective financial knowledge on social media and using financial knowledge advice on social media in life. It also means that it has a 64.8% chance that will enhance the action of taking financial knowledge sharing on the social media platform. In the Second Model, both levels of agreement in gaining effective financial knowledge on social media and the level of trust in the content creator have a positive correlation with the behavior of using financial knowledge advice on social media in life. It means that 75.9% chances enhance the action of taking financial knowledge shared on social media. </p><p>R2 is the coefficient of determination that explains the variations in the dependent variable accounted for by the independent variable. In the first model, an R square of 0.42 means that 42% of the knowledge sharing is accounted for by the level of agreement on social media. In model 2 there is a 57.7% chance provided by dependent variables, namely levels of agreement in gaining effective financial knowledge on social media and the level of trust in the content creator, to enhance the action of taking financial knowledge shared on social media.</p><p>Adjusted R2 adjusts the number of independent variables. It will select the new variable added to the model, and each predictor added in will greatly enhance the prediction of the final result. Thus the adjusted R2 gradually increases from model to model 8. The 8 model includes 8 different predictors, and the last model has achieved a value of 0.687 which means that 68.7% of the variation in financial knowledge shared on social media can be explained by the predictors. From this model, we can see that the second influenced factor is the trust in the influencer. When we added it to the model, it can be seen clearly that the adjusted R square has increased from .414 to .568. It is a significant growth compared to other predictors added to the model. </p><p>A significant F-change represents how significantly the variables added in have improved the prediction We specified the null hypothesis H0 as the model is not useful in the hypothesis testing and alternative hypothesis Ha as the model is useful. In this case, the 8 values in the 8 models of the significant F change here are all smaller than α=0.05 (significance level) which means we reject the H0 and accept Ha. It can be explained that the 8 models are effective, and the 8 predictors can affect the financial knowledge shared on social media. </p><h2 id="5-Qualitative-Analysis"><a href="#5-Qualitative-Analysis" class="headerlink" title="5     Qualitative Analysis"></a>5     Qualitative Analysis</h2><p>In this part, we are going to analyze factors that attract people to engage on social media Platforms like Dou yin. First, we are going to explain the successful operation mechanism behind Dou yin is the powerful algorithms. Then I will combine the data I have collected from my questionnaires and analyze the virtual communities.</p><h3 id="5-1-Algorithms-in-Dou-yin"><a href="#5-1-Algorithms-in-Dou-yin" class="headerlink" title="5.1    Algorithms in Dou yin"></a>5.1    Algorithms in Dou yin</h3><p>First of all, people spend a lot of time on Dou yin because of its powerful AI algorithms. Besides that, the content distribution strategy also plays a key role inside Dou yin. Compared with the “selection” mechanism of traditional Internet products, Byte’s “algorithm” can calculate users’ preferences according to their behavior path such as hesitating or rewatching a video. It can then recommend similar videos based on this information. </p><p>Thus, users can receive the pushed videos by the system’s personalized recommendation content automatically. It can save time and energy for the users however, these behaviors will be recorded by Dou yin’s background program. The longer time the users use Dou yin, the more data they accumulate. By deeply mining these data, Dou yin can determine which content users are more interested in, and then push the content out to what they may like. Dou yin’s algorithm takes personalized recommendations as to the focus of user services and carries out the overall distribution of various products and reviews on its operation.</p><p>According to the algorithm principle proposed by Byte Dance, they will characterize different users based on their interests, identity characteristics, and behavior characteristics[23]. The system will characterize the users based on the types of creators they subscribe to or topics they are interested in etc… The users have the freedom to subscribe to the followers they are fond of and pay more attention to their sharing. Users who have the same preferences will form their communities and share their common interests on the platform and different communities are being formed in this process.  </p><h3 id="5-2-Communities-of-Practice"><a href="#5-2-Communities-of-Practice" class="headerlink" title="5.2    Communities of Practice"></a>5.2    Communities of Practice</h3><p>Communities of practice are a group of people sharing common interests or regarding a particular topic such as wealth management. They can interact frequently within the communities to deepen their knowledge in this area and learn how to perform things better[24].</p><p>Unlike the traditional approach of management, communists of practice are only responsible for themselves. Thus, self-regulation will be an important characteristic in this case. Wenger has proposed COP from three dimensions. The first dimension is about a shared and negotiated understanding of what constitutes a joint enterprise and the relationships of mutual accountability [25][26].</p><p>The second point is about the mutual engagement which can define modes for both diverse and complex situations. The third point is about a shared repertoire that is embodied in a different language, routines, artifacts, tools, stories, and styles [27][25]. The importance of these three dimensions indicates the reciprocity and mutuality in communist practice in terms of regulation. </p><p>Identifying the communities is important and can also help to enhance the strategic development of the organizations [28][29]. Social media such as Dou yin should pay more attention to the degrees of formality and trust. However, we know that the informal role of Dou yin highly increases the process of knowledge diffusion. Limiting their informality can limit the engagement of people. So social media platforms like Dou yin can create some incentives for the participants in the community by letting them understand that knowledge sharing is part of the requirements for everyone on this platform [30]. This incentive will motivate the content creator for better productions of their content which can provide a better knowledge-sharing environment.</p><p>In social media such as Dou yin, there are mainly three roles in the community: the mentor, the member, and the lurkers. In common, the influencer in Dou yin will act as a role of mentor in the core of the community. They usually put their attention on their specialty and focus on the topic in a specific area. In this way, the community will be formed with an explicit style and characteristic to attract people with similar interests. The members are the people who have an interest in the topic and at the same time own the capability and knowledge about it. Thus, they usually have more passion, and they have a higher level of engagement than the lurkers in the community. In the Dou yin platform, members are in the middle of the community of practice. They are the ones appealing to the lurkers to join the community. Lastly is about the lurkers. Lurkers are the ones who usually observe the content but do not participate directly with the community. Researchers considered the lurkers as a passive form of participation to allow the online content, especially in Dou yin pass to the other users[31], [32]. They are of a significant role in passing the knowledge from different communities as they possess more time and energy for this activity. </p><h3 id="5-3-Virtual-sense-of-community"><a href="#5-3-Virtual-sense-of-community" class="headerlink" title="5.3    Virtual sense of community"></a>5.3    Virtual sense of community</h3><p>A virtual community is a social network consisting of people who can connect through specific social media such as Dou yin. It is usually dispersed geographically, different from the original sense of communities. In this virtual community like Dou yin, it offers the advantage of instant information exchange, also the response time can be very fast. Also, users can choose to access many discussion groups to form different specialized relationships according to their interests. These online communities can give users a feeling of membership and belongings where they will feel welcomed and received support from each other[33]. </p><p>For a virtual community, the first factor is having a common domain of interest. An accepted and bounded domain of interest must exist to create and maintain a sense of community. For example, if a user is interested in the topic of financial management, he or she can join the corresponding community to accept investment knowledge. Without a certain domain, the users in Dou yin will be lost in the large content of distribution. The second factor is having Continuous interaction, it will bring all the members together and strengthen the bonds between each other and with the influencer. It will nourish emotional attachment and social recognition and make the connection stronger. The third factor is the emotional support, interaction among community members will build into an emotional gain for all members. The better emotional support a member attains, the stronger the sense of community will be [34] Successful virtual communities will give their members a safe place to express their opinions and receive emotional support from their peers. Trust among members is essential to promote knowledge sharing, as people are more willing to interact in a familiar and trustable environment. </p><p>The fourth factor is the shared history and culture[35]. Virtual communities create their version of shared history that may be different from the physical communities. Another aspect apart from shared history is the shared culture. Virtual communities with a well-established culture will set specific expectations to let their members abide by. The use of terms or language may reveal a person to be a member of the community or an outsider. So, combining the history and the culture of the virtual community should both be counted. The fifth factor is about the virtually constructed identity. The reputation, status, and role of a virtual persona are almost as important as the physical characters being established in a sense of community. Thus, in Dou yin identity should be revealed, especially for the KOL in which they can build trust and more engagement with members of the community. These five elements are crucial to maintaining a successful ongoing sustainable virtual community with active engagement. </p><h2 id="6-Discussion"><a href="#6-Discussion" class="headerlink" title="6    Discussion"></a>6    Discussion</h2><p>In this part, I will combine the previously mentioned content in my paper including both the quantitative analysis of my designed questions in the questionnaires and the qualitative part about the definition to further explain my research topic. In figure 6 there are 4 different factors that influence users’ behavior on social media about wealth management. The value of 1 to 5 represents the degree of agreeableness in influencing the behavior of using knowledge sharing in Dou yin. The higher the value, means the more agreeableness it can influence the behavior of using knowledge sharing in Dou yin. </p><p><img src="file:////Users/dianazhang/Library/Group%20Containers/UBF8T346G9.Office/TemporaryItems/msohtmlclip/clip_image011.jpg" alt="Table  Description automatically generated"></p><p>Figure 6: Influenced factors of knowledge sharing </p><p><strong>The most influential factor</strong> is the level of trust in the influencers. There are 30 people over 103 people in total which gives out the highest score of 5. The average score of trust is 3.47 and it is the highest average score among the other factors.  In the sense of a virtual community, trust among members is essential to promote knowledge sharing, as people are more willing to interact in a familiar and trustable environment[36]. In the previous quantitative part, using the Pearson’s correlation method. The predictor for trust has a 63.3% relationship with the Y variable. It is almost the second largest influential factor apart from the quality of video content which accounts for 63.7%. This result shows that the trust of the influencer in the virtual community is of great significance. Thus, the influencers must know and enhance the trust in Dou yin to have a better engagement in knowledge sharing and dissemination. </p><p>There are two aspects to building trust in the virtual community. The first aspect is from the technical side, the Dou yin platform must maintain its security control and avoid data loss. So, before the user login into the platform, it needs to ensure the authentication from the users to recognize a valid user’s identity. More importantly, the authentication information should be kept confidentially with encryption and avoid the situation of data leakage [37]. </p><p>The second aspect is to ensure the importance of trust in the community which is from the human side based on the culture and morality. Trust encompasses not only people’s beliefs about others but also their willingness to use the knowledge shared by the influencers in the action of their life[38]. The virtual community may construct perceived integrity by imposing a code of ethical conduct. It means the influencers should share the knowledge in an ethical way instead of misleading the members of the community and destroying the trust in the community. When trust is broken it is hard to mend and recover the bounded relationship. Thereby in the Dou yin platform, it needs to build a perception of justice and enhance the trust between the members and the influencers in the community[39].</p><p><strong>The second most influential factor</strong> is having a high quality the video content. It has an average score of 3.37 out of 5. To examine if a knowledge-sharing video is of high quality it can be measured in two ways [40]. Firstly, is about the context. In Dou yin, each influencer will have different topics of knowledge-based videos to attract users with similar interests to join their communities. So, we must define the context, in this paper the topic will be wealth management the content should be established based on the context[41]. </p><p>Secondly is to have good video content. To have better content, the context must be narrowed down to create a more explicit vision to gain a competitive advantage in the relevant field. So, question no.5 shown in the appendix is being designed in the questionnaires, it is about the way of managing wealth. From the collected data, most than half of the people choose to put their capital in the bank saving accounts. In addition, there are around 45% of people invested in funds, around 26% of the people invested in stock, and 23% of the people invested in insurance. So, in this case, the influencer can make a more detailed extension of knowledge sharing topics on financial products. It should be the funds, stock, and insurance. </p><p><strong>The third influential factor</strong> is the content creator. It achieves an average score of 3.28. However, it has the lowest correlation as the predictor among the other three variables with 58.6% of the relationship. The concept of authenticity is defined as a  social construct fluctuating between the user, influencer, and the community [43]. In the virtual community like Dou yin. If the influencers disclose their true personal information and profile background to the public. It can enhance the level of trust between each other; thus, the audiences will be more willing to adopt the knowledge sharing into action from the influencers.</p><p><strong>The fourth influential factor</strong> is building an interacting community. It has achieved an average score of 3.03 out of 4 with the least number of only 17 people n a total of 103 strongly agree with this point. We can conclude that in the Dou yin platform, building a high level of trust in the community and providing a high quality of video content will push the whole community into an interactive community.</p><p>In the quantitative part of this paper, the analysis has come out that people acquiring financial knowledge from bank customer managers and the financial institution are more likely to adopt the financial knowledge shared on social media. In contrast, people who learn financial knowledge from the news and people who do self-research aren’t likely to adopt knowledge sharing from social media.</p><p>Figure 7 is a cross-over analysis. The X variable is different channels for acquiring financial knowledge and the Y variable is the degree of using financial knowledge in social media. The data is from the 103 respondents, and it shows that around 42% of people who acquire financial knowledge from bank customers strongly agree that social media can help them gain effective financial knowledge. Thus, the operation team and the KOL from Dou yin can target their audiences related to channels of acquiring knowledge from banks and financial institutions. It is easy to transfer and enlarge this group of people to learn financial knowledge in a virtual community such as Dou yin. </p><p><img src="file:////Users/dianazhang/Library/Group%20Containers/UBF8T346G9.Office/TemporaryItems/msohtmlclip/clip_image013.jpg" alt="Chart, bar chart  Description automatically generated"></p><p>Figure 7: Different channels affecting using KM</p><h2 id="7-Conclusion"><a href="#7-Conclusion" class="headerlink" title="7    Conclusion"></a>7    Conclusion</h2><p>In the questionnaire, question no.13 in the appendix, more than half of the people agree that regulators should continue to strengthen video audits related to financial knowledge sharing on social media. Thus, in Dou yin, the platform must set rules and regulations for the influencers to follow especially on topics related to investment. Social media platforms should ensure that the information shared in the community is rationalized instead of misleading or induced information to the public. Punishment and reward mechanisms should both exist in the system, and each performs its functions and duties. </p><p>This paper aims to enhance the investment awareness of the Chinese citizens by promoting knowledge sharing about wealth management on social media such as Dou yin. At the same time, they can also better understand the economic development in society and be the master of their own life. The paper also mentions the factors that the social media platform, the influencers, and the users must understand to make knowledge sharing more effective in the virtual community.</p><p>There are also limitations in this report, the collected data of the sample size is not large enough to represent the whole population of the Chinese citizens. Also, among the predictors, the variables can exist in interdependent relations with each other which may cause bias in the result. </p><h2 id="8-Reference"><a href="#8-Reference" class="headerlink" title="8    Reference"></a>8    Reference</h2><p>[1]   China Academy of Financial Research, “Investigation Report on Investment and Financial Management Behaviors of Chinese Residents_202107-2”.</p><p>[2]   L. Kuijs, H. Kharas, and T. Wang, “INVESTMENT AND SAVING IN CHINA * I thank Bert Hofman for encouragement and comments,” 2005. [Online]. Available: <a href="http://econ.worldbank.org/">http://econ.worldbank.org</a>.</p><p>[3]   Hamid. Faruqee, <em>Global Rebalancing : a Roadmap for Economic Recovery.</em> International Monetary Fund, 2013.</p><p>[4]   E. Okyere-Kwakye and K. Md Nor, “Individual Factors and Knowledge Sharing,” <em>American Journal of Economics and Business Administration</em>, vol. 3, no. 1, pp. 66–72, 2011.</p><p>[5]   China Internet Network Information Center, “The 47th Statistical Report on China’s Internet Development,” 2021.</p><p>[6]   Annette Chacko, “Understanding Douyin Marketing &amp; Audience Insights,” 2021, Accessed: Dec. 10, 2021. [Online]. Available: <a href="https://www.repustate.com/blog/douyin-marketing-platform/">https://www.repustate.com/blog/douyin-marketing-platform/</a></p><p>[7]   X. Lu and Z. Lu, “Fifteen Seconds of Fame: A Qualitative Study of Douyin, A Short Video Sharing Mobile Application in China,” in <em>Lecture Notes in Computer Science (including subseries Lecture Notes in Artificial Intelligence and Lecture Notes in Bioinformatics)</em>, 2019, vol. 11578 LNCS, pp. 233–244. doi: 10.1007/978-3-030-21902-4_17.</p><p>[8]   “2020_douyin_data_report”.</p><p>[9]   Z. Gaál, L. Szabó, N. Obermayer-Kovács, and A. Csepregi, “Exploring the Role of Social Media in Knowledge Sharing.” [Online]. Available: <a href="http://www.ejkm.com/">www.ejkm.com</a></p><p>[10]  Q. Yao, R. Y. M. Li, L. Song, and M. J. C. Crabbe, “Safety knowledge sharing on Twitter: A social network analysis,” <em>Safety Science</em>, vol. 143, Nov. 2021, doi: 10.1016/j.ssci.2021.105411.</p><p>[11]  M. K. Imran, S. M. J. Iqbal, U. Aslam, and T. Fatima, “Does social media promote knowledge exchange? A qualitative insight,” <em>Management Decision</em>, vol. 57, no. 3, pp. 688–702, Feb. 2019, doi: 10.1108/MD-05-2017-0477.</p><p>[12]  C. K. Faith and A. K. Seeam, “Knowledge sharing in academia: A case study using a SECI model approach,” 2018.</p><p>[13]  S. L. Hoe, “TACIT KNOWLEDGE, NONAKA AND TAKEUCHI SECI MODEL AND INFORMAL KNOWLEDGE PROCESSES,” 2006.</p><p>[14]  E. A. Smith, “The role of tacit and explicit knowledge in the workplace.” [Online]. Available: <a href="http://www.emerald-library.com/ft">http://www.emerald-library.com/ft</a></p><p>[15]  S. Chatterjee, N. P. Rana, and Y. K. Dwivedi, “Social media as a tool of knowledge sharing in academia: an empirical study using valance, instrumentality and expectancy (VIE) approach,” <em>Journal of Knowledge Management</em>, vol. 24, no. 10, pp. 2531–2552, Nov. 2020, doi: 10.1108/JKM-04-2020-0252.</p><p>[16]  S. Alina, “UNIVERSITY OF FINANCE AND ADMINISTRATION Faculty of Economic Studies Field of Study: Business Management and Corporate Finance Bachelor´s study programme in the full-time form.”</p><p>[17]  H. Mohajan and H. K. Mohajan, “Munich Personal RePEc Archive A Comprehensive Analysis of Knowledge Management Cycles A Comprehensive Analysis of Knowledge Management Cycles,” 2017.</p><p>[18]  S. Aujirapongpan, P. Vadhanasindhu, A. Chandrachai, and P. Cooparat, “Indicators of knowledge management capability for KM effectiveness,” <em>VINE</em>, vol. 40, no. 2. pp. 183–203, 2010. doi: 10.1108/03055721011050677.</p><p>[19]  M. M. Evans, K. Dalkir, and C. Bidian, “A Holistic View of the Knowledge Life Cycle: The Knowledge Management Cycle (KMC) Model,” 1993. [Online]. Available: <a href="http://www.ejkm.com/">www.ejkm.com</a></p><p>[20]  J. Banister, D. E. Bloom, and L. Rosenberg, “PROGRAM ON THE GLOBAL DEMOGRAPHY OF AGING Population Aging and Economic Growth in China,” 2010. [Online]. Available: <a href="http://www.hsph.harvard.edu/pgda/working.htm">http://www.hsph.harvard.edu/pgda/working.htm</a></p><p>[21]  S. Chen, “Aging with Chinese characteristics: A public policy perspective,” <em>Ageing International</em>, vol. 34, no. 3, pp. 172–188, Sep. 2009, doi: 10.1007/s12126-009-9043-6.</p><p>[22]  J. J. Berman, “Understanding Your Data,” in <em>Data Simplification</em>, Elsevier, 2016, pp. 135–187. doi: 10.1016/B978-0-12-803781-2.00004-7.</p><p>[23]  Z. Zhao, “Analysis on the douyin (Tiktok) Mania Phenomenon Based on Recommendation Algorithms,” in <em>E3S Web of Conferences</em>, Feb. 2021, vol. 235. doi: 10.1051/e3sconf/202123503029.</p><p>[24]  H. Mohajan and H. Kumar Mohajan, “Munich Personal RePEc Archive Roles of Communities of Practice for the Development of the Society Roles of Communities of Practice for the Development of the Society,” 2017.</p><p>[25]  D. Ellis, R. Oldridge, and A. Vasconcelos, “Community and Virtual Community.”</p><p>[26]  M. Graven, “Communities of practice: Learning, meaning and identity,” <em>Journal of Mathematics Teacher Education</em>, vol. 6, no. 2, pp. 185–194, 2003, doi: 10.1023/A:1023947624004.</p><p>[27]  E. Wenger, “Communities of Practice and Social Learning Systems,” <em>Organization</em>, vol. 7, no. 2, pp. 225–246, May 2000, doi: 10.1177/135050840072002.</p><p>[28]  “Communities of Practice - the organizational frontier by Wenger”.</p><p>[29]  J. S. Brown and P. Duguid, “Organizing Knowledge,” <em>California Management Review</em>, vol. 40, no. 3, pp. 90–111, Apr. 1998, doi: 10.2307/41165945.</p><p>[30]  E. Davenport and H. Hall, “Organizational knowledge and communities of practice,” <em>Annual Review of Information Science and Technology</em>, vol. 36. Information Today, pp. 170–227, 2002. doi: 10.1002/aris.1440360105.</p><p>[31]  W. Gong, E.-P. Lim, and F. Zhu, “Characterizing Silent Users in Social Media Communities.” [Online]. Available: <a href="http://www.aaai.org/">www.aaai.org</a></p><p>[32]  V. Soroka and S. Rafaeli, “Invisible participants,” in <em>Proceedings of the 15th international conference on World Wide Web - WWW ’06</em>, 2006, p. 163. doi: 10.1145/1135777.1135806.</p><p>[33]  L. Tonteri, M. Kosonen, H. K. Ellonen, and A. Tarkiainen, “Antecedents of an experienced sense of virtual community,” <em>Computers in Human Behavior</em>, vol. 27, no. 6, pp. 2215–2223, Nov. 2011, doi: 10.1016/j.chb.2011.06.018.</p><p>[34]  D. Rotman and P. F. Wu, “SenSe of Community in Virtual enVironmentS.”</p><p>[35]  X. Zhang, J. Tang, X. Wei, M. Yi, and P. Ordóñez, “How does mobile social media affect knowledge sharing under the ‘Guanxi’ system?,” <em>Journal of Knowledge Management</em>, vol. 24, no. 6, pp. 1343–1367, Jul. 2020, doi: 10.1108/JKM-02-2020-0118.</p><p>[36]  M. Jami Pour and F. Taheri, “Personality traits and knowledge sharing behavior in social media: mediating role of trust and subjective well-being,” <em>On the Horizon</em>, vol. 27, no. 2, pp. 98–117, Jul. 2019, doi: 10.1108/OTH-03-2019-0012.</p><p>[37]  I. Mezgár, “Trust building in virtual communities,” in <em>IFIP Advances in Information and Communication Technology</em>, 2009, vol. 307, pp. 393–400. doi: 10.1007/978-3-642-04568-4_41.</p><p>[38]  N. Mohammad and Y. Stedham, “Relationship between Cultural Values, Sense of Community and Trust and the Effect of Trust in Workplace.” [Online]. Available: <a href="https://hal.archives-ouvertes.fr/hal-03257439">https://hal.archives-ouvertes.fr/hal-03257439</a></p><p>[39]  J. J. Wu, Y. H. Chen, and Y. S. Chung, “Trust factors influencing virtual community members: A study of transaction communities,” <em>Journal of Business Research</em>, vol. 63, no. 9–10, pp. 1025–1032, Sep. 2010, doi: 10.1016/j.jbusres.2009.03.022.</p><p>[40]  E. Agichtein, C. Castillo, D. Donato, and A. Gionis, “Finding High-Quality Content in Social Media.” [Online]. Available: <a href="http://answers.yahoo.com/">http://answers.yahoo.com/</a></p><p>[41]  “DAVID LEWIS INDEX, CONTEXT, AND CONTENT,” 1980.</p><p>[42]  A. E. Marwick, “‘They’re really profound women, they’re entrepreneurs’: Conceptions of Authenticity in Fashion Blogging,” 2013. [Online]. Available: <a href="http://www.aaai.org/">www.aaai.org</a></p><p>[43]  M. Nouri, “Scholar Commons The Power of Influence: Traditional Celebrity vs Social Media Influencer.” [Online]. Available: <a href="https://scholarcommons.scu.edu/engl_176/32">https://scholarcommons.scu.edu/engl_176/32</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>Research</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Biodegradable material mycelium in fashion industry</title>
    <link href="/2023/04/12/biodegradable_material_mycelium_in_the_fashion_industry/"/>
    <url>/2023/04/12/biodegradable_material_mycelium_in_the_fashion_industry/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="The-application-of-biodegradable-material-mycelium-in-the-fashion-industry-A-case-study-of-Bolt-Threads-Company-proposal"><a href="#The-application-of-biodegradable-material-mycelium-in-the-fashion-industry-A-case-study-of-Bolt-Threads-Company-proposal" class="headerlink" title="The application of biodegradable material mycelium in the fashion industry - A case study of Bolt Threads Company(proposal)"></a>The application of biodegradable material mycelium in the fashion industry - A case study of Bolt Threads Company(proposal)</h1><h2 id="Keywords"><a href="#Keywords" class="headerlink" title="Keywords:"></a>Keywords:</h2><p>Biodegradable material, Sustainable environment, the Fashion industry, Bolt Threads company</p><h2 id="Abstract"><a href="#Abstract" class="headerlink" title="Abstract:"></a>Abstract:</h2><p>This study report wants to find out what is the current usage situation of mycelium in the fashion industry and what will its future look like. Will it have a broader applicable market in the relatively developed regions by using biodegradable material to promote sustainable consciousness for people. Since fashion makes a sizeable contribution to climate change the whole industry is facing the transition risk. Therefore, using sustainable materials like mycelium can be an environmentally friendly alternative to materials like animal-based leather. Mycelium-based materials can be produced either as pure materials from liquid cultures of mycelium or as composites based on organic substrates. The process is simple to conduct by using little energy and water and it is fast growing and in massive production. This paper will examine the application of mycelium in the market and takes Bolt Threads company as an example in the fashion industry. Besides, the future development of mycelium including its opportunities and challenges will also be illustrated.</p><h2 id="Introduction"><a href="#Introduction" class="headerlink" title="Introduction:"></a>Introduction:</h2><p>The growing population and rapid development of technology have led to an immense increase in greenhouse gas emissions and have caused serious climate change issues on our planet. The global fashion industry also called the textile industry is closely related to our daily life, over the past two decades, there has been an increasing consumer demand in the fashion industry (Gardetti &amp; Muthu, 2020).  Consumption is on the opposite side of sustainability. The fashion industry is concerned by the negative environmental and social impact it brings as it produces nearly 10% of CO2 annually (Niinimäki et al., 2020). The fashion industry is the second most polluting industry which has caused 20% of all global wastewater, with an anticipated 50% increase in greenhouse gas emissions by 2030 (Bailey et al., 2022).</p><h2 id="Literature-review"><a href="#Literature-review" class="headerlink" title="Literature review:"></a>Literature review:</h2><p><strong>Outline:</strong></p><ol><li><p>The changing environment ( Sustainability; Climate change issue )</p></li><li><p>The development of the sustainable fashion industry (compare with the fast industry)</p></li><li><p>The consumption behavior and environmental consciousness of consumers</p></li><li><p>The use of biodegradable material (comparison with other materials)</p></li></ol><p> Climate change is a global issue and we need to take a polycentric system to take action in reducing the greenhouse gases (GHGs) being emitted to society (Ostrom, 2010).</p><p>Sustainable fashion which is part of slow fashion often seen on the opposite side of fast fashion. Slow fashion is a concept that advocates for environmental and social justice, it centers on sustainability values such as good working conditions for workers and reducing environmental damages to the society (Henninger et al., 2016). </p><p> Fast fashion consumers look for constant change and new products at a relatively lower price frequently. Thus, timing is a priority for the fast fashion brands like Zara, H&amp;M, etc. They need to get the costumes quickly and push for the latest trend (Bruce &amp; Daly, 2006). </p><p> On the other hand, consumer ethics in relation to fashion consumption is considered a slow culture (McNeill &amp; Moore, 2015). It takes time and education to minimize the attitude-behavior gap to be knowledgeable enough about innovative products for sustainable consumption (Shen et al., 2013).</p><p>The first thing to consider for sustainable fashion is the material. The choice of materials has a large impact on the overall footprint of clothing from cultivation land, fertilizer, and water use to processing energy, chemical, and water use to use microplastic pollution (Lacy et al., 2020). </p><p>For cotton biodegrades it requires nearly twice as much land as hemp per finished textiles. Cotton’s entire production process uses more than four times as much water as hemp. Most of the cotton is also not grown organically and relies on pesticides that will lead to negative effects on the environment and also human health (Parvin et al., 2020). Another issue with cotton is that while it will biodegrade, it’s treated with pesticides and dyes that can permeate soil once the fabric breaks down which damages the environment.</p><p> Animal agriculture is a leading contributor to climate change, and beef and leather-producing cattle are especially linked to global warming, deforestation, and water pollution. The Food and Agriculture Organization estimates that animal agriculture is responsible for between 14.5 percent and 18 percent of global greenhouse gas emissions, but 65 percent of that comes from cattle (Farra, 2021). While traditional leather and its alternatives are mainly produced from animals or synthetic materials, mycelium-based leather alternatives are fabricated through upcycling agriculture and forestry resembling leather in both the aesthetic texture and its properties.  </p><h2 id="Methodology"><a href="#Methodology" class="headerlink" title="Methodology:"></a>Methodology:</h2><p>This study report mainly focuses on using qualitative methods emphasizing exploratory research by using a case study approach to explore the future application of biodegradable material mycelium in the fashion industry, with a specific focus on Bolt Threads Company. Literature research will be conducted to collect information from commercial and academic articles. Besides, using descriptive research including secondary data from the company website and other industry reports to know more about the consumers’ preferences and behavior toward biodegradable materials in the fashion industry. </p><h2 id="Case-Study"><a href="#Case-Study" class="headerlink" title="Case Study:"></a>Case Study:</h2><p> Bolt Threads is a California-based company that creates sustainable materials by engineering proteins inspired by nature. They invent cutting-edge materials for the fashion and beauty industries to put us on a path toward a more sustainable future. One of their products is called Mylo™ which is a leather alternative made from mycelium, the complex thread structure that allows fungi to grow (Chung, 2021). It is a high-quality alternative for animal and synthetic-based leather that has the potential to become commercially viable. Mylo is soft, supple, and free of harmful chemicals usually used in leather production. It emits fewer greenhouse gases and uses less water and resources than animal leather.</p><p> Mycelium is a type of fungus that grows underground and forms a network of thread-like structures. It has been found to have several properties that make it suitable for use in the fashion industry (Antinori et al., 2020). Mycelium is biodegradable, which means that it can decompose naturally in the environment, and it is lightweight and flexible thus it is suitable to be used in clothing and accessories. Also it can be grown in a controlled environment, which makes it a sustainable alternative to traditional materials (Vandelook et al., 2021) and it usually takes a shorter time within two weeks to cultivate a massive amount. </p><p> Mylo has made a consortium with its partners such as Adidas, Kering, lululemon, and Stella McCartney. They are combined based on mission alignment, and high standards of quality. They are banded together to invest in meaningful material innovation with Mylo. Debuted by consortium partner Adidas in April 2021, the Stan Smith Mylo™ is the first-ever shoe made with Mylo. Adidas pays homage to a classic with a new pledge of responsibility to find material solutions inspired by nature (Thread, 2022).</p><h2 id="Conclusion"><a href="#Conclusion" class="headerlink" title="Conclusion:"></a>Conclusion:</h2><p>Opportunities: Mycelium has a unique texture that can be manipulated to create different finishes, making it an interesting material for fashion designers to work with. The texture of mycelium can be manipulated to mimic the look and feel of other materials, such as leather or suede, which can be appealing to consumers. Incorporating mycelium into fashion designs can also help fashion brands improve their sustainability and eco-friendly credentials, which is becoming increasingly important to consumers. Brands that use sustainable and eco-friendly materials are likely to be viewed more positively by consumers and are more likely to attract environmentally conscious consumers. The use of mycelium in the fashion industry is still a relatively new concept, which presents opportunities for designers to create new and innovative products that stand out in a crowded market. Designers can experiment with different shapes, sizes, and textures, which can help create new and exciting fashion products.</p><p>Challenges: Mycelium is currently produced in small batches, making it difficult to scale up production to meet the demands of the fashion industry. New production methods need to be developed to address this issue. Also, the production can be expensive, which can make it challenging for designers to incorporate mycelium into their designs and for consumers to afford mycelium-based products. Cost-effective production methods need to be developed to address this issue as well.</p><p>Solutions: While mycelium is a durable material, it may not be as durable as some traditional materials. This means that products made from mycelium may have a shorter lifespan. Designers need to ensure that mycelium-based products are durable and can withstand normal wear and tear. Also, consumers may be hesitant to purchase products made from a relatively unknown material. Designers and manufacturers need to educate consumers about the benefits of mycelium-based materials and address any concerns they may have about the safety and quality of these products. The problems need to be addressed for the mycelium to become a more widely adopted material in the fashion industry. Despite these challenges, the potential benefits of mycelium-based materials make them an exciting and promising area of innovation for the fashion industry.</p><h2 id="References"><a href="#References" class="headerlink" title="References:"></a>References:</h2><p> Antinori, M. E., Ceseracciu, L., Mancini, G., Heredia-Guerrero, J. A., &amp; Athanassiou, A. (2020). Fine-tuning of physicochemical properties and growth dynamics of mycelium-based materials. <em>ACS Applied Bio Materials</em>, <em>3</em>(2), 1044-1051. </p><p>Bailey, K., Basu, A., &amp; Sharma, S. (2022). The Environmental Impacts of Fast Fashion on Water Quality: A Systematic Review. <em>Water</em>, <em>14</em>(7), 1073. </p><p>Bruce, M., &amp; Daly, L. (2006). Buyer behaviour for fast fashion. <em>Journal of Fashion Marketing and Management: An International Journal</em>, <em>10</em>(3), 329-344. </p><p>Chung, E. (2021). Made of fungi, mycelium hits market as green substitute for leather, plastic. <em>CBC News</em>. <a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/science/mycelium-fungi-green-materials-1.5954664">https://www.cbc.ca/news/science/mycelium-fungi-green-materials-1.5954664</a></p><p>Farra, E. (2021). <em>Stella McCartney Introduces Her First Garments Made Of Mylo, The “Leather” Alternative Grown From Mushrooms</em>. <a href="https://www.vogue.co.uk/fashion/article/stella-mccartney-first-mylo-mushroom-leather-alternative-ready-to-wear">https://www.vogue.co.uk/fashion/article/stella-mccartney-first-mylo-mushroom-leather-alternative-ready-to-wear</a></p><p>Gardetti, M. A., &amp; Muthu, S. S. (2020). <em>The UN sustainable development goals for the textile and fashion industry</em>. Springer. </p><p>Henninger, C. E., Alevizou, P. J., &amp; Oates, C. J. (2016). What is sustainable fashion? <em>Journal of Fashion Marketing and Management: An International Journal</em>, <em>20</em>(4), 400-416. </p><p>Lacy, P., Long, J., Spindler, W., Lacy, P., Long, J., &amp; Spindler, W. (2020). Fashion industry profile. <em>The Circular Economy Handbook: Realizing the Circular Advantage</em>, 185-195. </p><p>McNeill, L., &amp; Moore, R. (2015). Sustainable fashion consumption and the fast fashion conundrum: fashionable consumers and attitudes to sustainability in clothing choice. <em>International Journal of Consumer Studies</em>, <em>39</em>(3), 212-222. </p><p>Mukendi, A., Davies, I., Glozer, S., &amp; McDonagh, P. (2020). Sustainable fashion: current and future research directions. <em>European Journal of Marketing</em>. </p><p>Niinimäki, K., Peters, G., Dahlbo, H., Perry, P., Rissanen, T., &amp; Gwilt, A. (2020). The environmental price of fast fashion. <em>Nature Reviews Earth &amp; Environment</em>, <em>1</em>(4), 189-200. </p><p>Ostrom, E. (2010). Polycentric systems for coping with collective action and global environmental change. <em>Global environmental change</em>, <em>20</em>(4), 550-557. </p><p>Parvin, F., Islam, S., Akm, S. I., Urmy, Z., &amp; Ahmed, S. (2020). A study on the solutions of environment pollutions and worker’s health problems caused by textile manufacturing operations. <em>Biomed. J. Sci. Tech. Res</em>, <em>28</em>, 21831-21844. </p><p>Shen, D., Richards, J., &amp; Liu, F. (2013). Consumers’ awareness of sustainable fashion. <em>Marketing Management Journal</em>, <em>23</em>(2), 134-147. </p><p>Thread, B. (2022). <em>Bolt technology</em>. <a href="https://boltthreads.com/technology/mylo/">https://boltthreads.com/technology/mylo/</a></p><p>Vandelook, S., Elsacker, E., Van Wylick, A., De Laet, L., &amp; Peeters, E. (2021). Current state and future prospects of pure mycelium materials. <em>Fungal biology and biotechnology</em>, <em>8</em>(1), 1-10. </p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>Sustainability</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>The analysis of Electric-motorcycle(Yadea-Y1S)in the UK market</title>
    <link href="/2022/11/14/Yadea_analysis/"/>
    <url>/2022/11/14/Yadea_analysis/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="The-Market-Audit"><a href="#The-Market-Audit" class="headerlink" title="The Market Audit:"></a><strong>The Market Audit:</strong></h2><p><strong>Summary:</strong></p><p>Our product is going to be sold in the UK which has a mature infrastructure for its communication and transportation system. The company also needs to be concerned about the environmental benefits and the after-sales service. All these factors can affect consumers’ purchasing habits. make cooperation with the company like <strong>Arcadis</strong> to build up the infrastructure and provide solutions to transportation issues. Finding agent middlemen, wholesalers and retailers can also have a huge impact on increasing the sales of Yadea’s Y1S. Percentage sales, early payment discounts, and wholesale discounts are critical to increasing sales in the UK market.  </p><h3 id="Describe-the-market-in-which-the-product-is-to-be-sold"><a href="#Describe-the-market-in-which-the-product-is-to-be-sold" class="headerlink" title="Describe the market in which the product is to be sold"></a>Describe the market in which the product is to be sold</h3><p>\1.   Geographical region: </p><p>The United Kingdom which comprises England, Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland locates in the Western part of the European countries which is surrounded by four seas. To the South is the English Channel, which separates it from continental Europe. to the East by the North Sea, and to the West by the Irish Sea and the Atlantic Ocean. The land has a total area of 243,610 km² and a total coastline of 12,429 km. </p><p>\2.   Forms of transportation and communication available in that region </p><p>Cycling is very popular in the UK which can both save money and keep you fit. Most UK towns and cities offer regular bus services and Taxis are easy to find in all major cities and towns also the UK has a large train network to travel across cities and towns. There are also 24 international airports in the UK which provide a variety of cheap flights. In addition, Eurostar’s high-speed train services running frequently can travel from London to the continent in just over two hours, every day of the week. </p><p>Under the country code +44, there were a total of 111.04 million connections in 2020. In addition to broadband Internet connections, around 95% of all residents have access to the Internet. Around 41% have a fast Internet connection.</p><p>\3.   Consumer buying habits</p><p>a.   Product-use pattern: Ecological and responsible consumption is growing, highly adaptable, and expandable, the Y1S can be modified for bike-sharing, takeaway operations, logistics, and other applications. Besides, it is mainly considered for commercial use by businesspeople in the UK. </p><p>b.   Product feature preference: The customers would care about the price, quality, design, brand, and environmental benefits it can bring to society. After-sales service should be focused, and claims are common if the product has problems. Yadea’s intelligent Battery Management System (BMS) ensures a safer ride with protection against overcurrent, overheating, overcharging, short-circuiting, and more.</p><p>c.   Shopping habits: The British are increasingly buying online; thus, online commerce is an important channel to advertise our company’s brand and promote the Yadea Y1S. The below graph is the top online payment methods used in the UK. The vendors in the UK will also look at the factors such as the Imported price, taxes, shipping cost, and the delivery period. </p><p><img src="/img/UK_Online_Payment_Methods_Used_Recently.png" alt="UK_Online_Payment_Methods_Used_Recently"></p><p>Figure 1- online payment methods used in the UK</p><p>\4.   Distribution of the product</p><p>a.   Typical retail outlets: There are 40000+ retailers and 3000+ distributors across the world. There are around 30+ UK deals of scooters that can be found in the England of the UK and there is also one that can be found in Whales. Building up the supply chain in the UK can distribute our product more efficiently. Thus, the manufacturers can make cooperation with a company like <strong>Arcadis</strong> to build up the infrastructure and provide solutions to transportation issues.</p><p>b.   Product sales by other middlemen: Finding agent middlemen for the scooter is a good approach to selling the product. Using Wholesalers who bought in more quantities and sell them to the retailer can also increase the chances of buying the scooter.</p><p>\5.   Advertising and promotion</p><p>a.   Advertising media: Facebook and Instagram are good tools for using the market strategy called Market push and pull. The algorithm technology can push the products to our potential customers and bring their interests into our YADEA Y1S.</p><p>b.   Sales promotion customarily used: coupons, samples, premiums, point-of-purchase (POP) displays, directly approach by sending emails to the vendors.</p><p>\6.   Pricing Strategy</p><p>a.   Customary markups: The price of the Yadea-Y1S is 3599 Euro, the operating cost will be 2880 and the net income will be 720Euro (5300RMB).720/3600=20% The customary markups for Yadea Y1s in UK is around 20%.</p><p>b.   Types of discounts available: Percentage sales, early payment discounts, wholesale discounts, and seasonal discounts; In this case, using the percentage sales and early payment discounts can be a good method. We can offer the vendors a 10 to 15 percent discount if they buy the cars within the promotion activity. Those who paid for the car early and more quantities in the limited time will get more discount. </p><hr><h2 id="The-Marketing-Plan"><a href="#The-Marketing-Plan" class="headerlink" title="The Marketing Plan:"></a><strong>The Marketing Plan:</strong></h2><p><strong>Summary:</strong></p><p>Yadea-Y1S targets the high-end market for the businessman to use and it is important to find the right customer in a short time. The UK market has the potential to grow in the future but to gain a competitive advantage in the market share, the company needs to expand its retail shops in the UK to attract more customers who the interests in using the electric motor car in life. Besides that, marketing techniques for example using coupons and personal selling will be helpful as well. Through estimation Yadea’s profit in 2022 in the UK market is expected to be <strong>40,834,256RMB</strong>. To maximize the probability of achieving this target, the company can use the SWOT analysis to know that as a listed company its strength is the strong research and development team and its weakness is the limited speed and the product outlook, its opportunity is the trend of the green transportation, and the threat is the international competitors and the political risk and policies that will affect the operation abroad. The product advantages and features are the large battery capacity and the intelligent Battery Management System, it is also dedicated to providing sustainable customer service together with its distributor partners. Our Wish is to increase Yadea’s leadership role in the industry, by creating a new generation that’s identified by a green commuting lifestyle. </p><h3 id="A-Marketing-objectives"><a href="#A-Marketing-objectives" class="headerlink" title="A. Marketing objectives"></a>A. Marketing objectives</h3><ol><li><p>Target market: Yadea-Y1S is suitable for commercial use, and it targets customers for businessmen and freelancers. The life cycle of the product is short as it belongs to a specialty good. Thus, it is of great importance to advertising our products to the exact consumers in a limited period.</p></li><li><p>Sales forecast years 1-5: The UK market has the potential to grow in the future due to the trend of the green transportation. We estimate the sales by using the forecast revenue from 2022 to 2026.  And divided by 26000RMB (3500 euro) for a single price of the Yadea-Y1S. We will probably sold 1570 electric-scooters in 2022 in the UK market.</p></li></ol><p><img src="/img/Sales_forecast_yadea_Y1S.png" alt="Sales_forecast_yadea_Y1S"></p><p>Figure 2- Sales Forecast from 2022 to 2026</p><ol start="3"><li>Profit forecast years 1-5: Currently, over 90% of the Group’s revenue and operating profit were generated from the sale of electric vehicles in the PRC. In the total revenue for electric scooters, we counted 2% total sales of the market share in the UK and 20% for the revenue of Yadea Y1S (10,208,564,000 * 2%* 20%) will be <strong>40,834,256RMB.</strong></li></ol><p><img src="/img/Revenue_forecast_Yadea_Y1S.png" alt="Revenue_forecast_Yadea_Y1S"></p><p>Figure 3- Revenue forecast from 2022 to 2026</p><ol start="4"><li>Market penetration and coverage: Moreover, with the emergence of demand for personalized green micro-mobility, continuous upgrade of electric two-wheeled vehicles, and diversification of product applications, the customer base will continue to expand. Further coupled with the sustainable replacement demand brought by the growing penetration of two-wheeled vehicles, the two-wheeled vehicles industry enjoys an optimistic outlook.</li></ol><h3 id="B-SWOT-Analysis"><a href="#B-SWOT-Analysis" class="headerlink" title="B.  SWOT Analysis"></a>B.  SWOT Analysis</h3><ol><li><p>Strengths: The Group had an annual electric two-wheeled vehicle production capacity of approximately 17 million units, supported by more than 9,000 employees. Accelerated technological innovations and advances - It also has a strong research and development team based in Shanghai and Wuxi with 906 research and development professionals with various product design backgrounds for electric two-wheeled vehicles. Also, the Company was listed on the Main Board of The Stock Exchange of Hong Kong which will increase its financing capital for its operation.</p></li><li><p>Weaknesses: The Business Model of Yadea Group can be easily imitated by competitors in the Recreational Products industry. To overcome these challenges company needs to build a platform model that can integrate suppliers, vendors, and end users. Also, the speed is limited to 45 km/h, and the outlook is not sporty. There is also a lack of charging stations in the UK.</p></li><li><p>Opportunities: Advocating for green traveling which retard the climate change issues. The launch of the Y1S comes as more countries introduce policies to promote the use of electric two-wheelers. According to the UNEP, a global shift to 90% electric two- and three-wheelers by 2030 will reduce CO2 emissions by 11 billion tons between now and 2050.</p></li><li><p>Threats: Competitors catching up with the product development - Even though at present the Yadea Group is still the leader in product innovation in the Recreational Products segment. It is facing stiff challenges from international and local competitors. The changing policy and the external political risk might affect the operation in the UK; thus the managers have to follow up with the macroeconomics of the society to adjust its marketing strategy.</p></li></ol><h3 id="C-Product-adaptation-or-modification"><a href="#C-Product-adaptation-or-modification" class="headerlink" title="C.  Product adaptation or modification"></a>C.  Product adaptation or modification</h3><ol><li><p>Core component:  The two detachable, lightweight dual-connected batteries offer large battery capacity, and the vehicle also allows for two intelligent charging modes – direct from the vehicle or charging from the battery base, so riders can go further for more convenient operation. At the same time, Yadea’s intelligent Battery Management System (BMS) ensures a safer ride with protection against overcurrent, overheating, overcharging, short-circuiting, and more. </p></li><li><p>Packaging component: Domestic waste is handed over to the local environmental sanitation department for regular treatment every month, while waste packaging materials are handed over to a third-party agency for recycling and reuse to achieve resource recycling. </p></li><li><p>Support services component: At the same time, the Group will provide distributors with training in technical support, distributor product shopping guide, store management, event promotion (including after-sales training and maintenance support), and promote the concept of sustainable customer service together with distributor partners to ensure that distributors can provide customers with good sales and after-sales experience, and promote high-standard service requirements to overseas distributors. It can also have add-ons like putting the huge refrigerant boxes at the back and it can improve its GPS control as well. </p></li></ol><h3 id="D-Promotion-mix"><a href="#D-Promotion-mix" class="headerlink" title="D.  Promotion mix"></a>D.  Promotion mix</h3><ol><li>Advertising</li></ol><p>a.   Objectives: Yadea Group is a high-end electric two-wheeler manufacturer integrating development, and production to create a Sustainable society. It can increase the brand reputation and get more attraction from local people.</p><p>b.   Media mix: Digital marketing can be targeted on Instagram and YouTube; while traditional marketing can be transit signage, direct mail, and TV and radio spots.</p><p>c.   Message: Our Wish is to increase Yadea’s leadership role in the industry, by creating a new generation that’s identified by a green commuting lifestyle.</p><p>d.   Costs: Take Yadea’s 2021 financial annual report as a reference the advertising expense will be <strong>729,440 RMB</strong> (364,720,000 * 1%* 20%) in 2022.</p><ol start="2"><li>Sales promotion</li></ol><p>a.   Objectives: To promote sales growth and attract new customers and retain customer loyalty. By sending emails, holding online tradeshows, and making improvements to the official website.</p><p>b.   Coupons: You can get the promotion code from the online website and then you can get a discount on the product Yadea Y1S. If not, the coupons can also be achieved from the promotion activities.</p><p>c.   Premiums: The main measures can include random inspection of the fire-fighting facilities in the distributor’s warehouses from time to time, promotion of explosion-proof cabinets for lithium batteries in stores, promotion of storage of batteries and other goods in different areas, purchase of relevant insurance, and organizing relevant training.</p><p>d.   Costs: According to the 2021 financial report of Yadea, the selling and distribution cost in the 2022 of UK is approximately <strong>25,600,000</strong> RMB (1.28 billion *1%*20%) including the increase in employee benefits expenses, advertising expenses, and travel expenses.</p><ol start="3"><li><p>Personal selling: First can build up the brand recognition and product awareness of Yadea Y1S, then stimulate the customer’s demand by building a relationship at the same time persuading and providing technical information about the electric motorbike. </p></li><li><p>Other promotional methods: (i) brand promotion, advertising, and marketing; (ii) expansion of the distributor points of sales overhaul campaign; (iii) expansion of the international sales; (iv) development of the online platform, including online sales promotion and marketing.</p></li></ol>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>Marketing</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>The UK&#39;s Economic</title>
    <link href="/2022/10/17/The_UKs_economic_Situation/"/>
    <url>/2022/10/17/The_UKs_economic_Situation/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="K-International-trade-statistics"><a href="#K-International-trade-statistics" class="headerlink" title="K: International trade statistics"></a>K: International trade statistics</h3><h4 id="1-Major-export"><a href="#1-Major-export" class="headerlink" title="1. Major export:"></a>1. Major export:</h4><p>From the data, we can see a growing trend in the export of goods and services from the year 2016 to 2019. There was an apparent shrinking in 2020 due to the outbreak of Covid-19. The global ranking of the UK in 2021 of exports in goods and services ranked 7th. The value of the UK’s total trade in the 12 months to the end of July 2022 is £1,441.9 billion, and the UK possesses £676.6 billion in export and £765.3billion in imports. Total exports of goods in July 2022 increased by £2.1 billion (6.7%), driven by a £1.3 billion (7.9%) increase in exports to EU countries, while exports to non-EU countries increased by £0.8 billion (5.4%)(Statistics, September 2022). The increase in exports to EU countries in 2022 was primarily driven by higher exports of fuels, machinery and transport equipment. The left table shows the top 5 UK exports of goods from 12 months to the end of July 2022. The right table is the top 5 UK services exports for four quarters to the end of March 2022(Statistics, October 2022). The UK’s top 5 trading partners for goods exports in 2021 are the United States, Germany, Netherlands, Ireland, and France. </p><table><thead><tr><th><strong>Top</strong>   <strong>5</strong> <strong>UK goods   exports</strong></th><th><strong>Value   (£ billion)</strong></th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>Mechanical  power generators</td><td>24.7</td></tr><tr><td>Crude  oil</td><td>24.7</td></tr><tr><td>Medicinal  and pharmaceutical products</td><td>23.1</td></tr><tr><td>Cars</td><td>21.8</td></tr><tr><td>Non-ferrous  metals</td><td>17.2</td></tr></tbody></table><table><thead><tr><th><strong>Top   5 UK services exports</strong></th><th><strong>Value   (£ billion)</strong></th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>Other  business services</td><td>126.8</td></tr><tr><td>Financial  services</td><td>61.3</td></tr><tr><td>Telecomms,  computer and information</td><td>31.0</td></tr><tr><td>Insurance  and pension services</td><td>21.9</td></tr><tr><td>Transport  services</td><td>19.2</td></tr></tbody></table><h4 id="2-Major-Imports"><a href="#2-Major-Imports" class="headerlink" title="2. Major Imports:"></a>2. Major Imports:</h4><p>There was a growing value of capital in goods and services from 2016 to 2019, and in 2020, there was a massive decline in imports of goods compared with services. The global ranking of 2021 of imported goods and services ranked 6th in the UK. Total imports of goods decreased by £0.5 billion (0.9%) in July 2022 because of a £0.4 billion (1.5%) fall in imports from non-EU countries, while imports from EU countries decreased by £0.1 billion (0.3%). Imports from non-EU countries were higher than imports from the EU due to the significant increases in the imports of fuels in the last months of 2021. The left table shows the top 5 UK goods imports from 12 months to the end of July 2022. The right table is the top 5 UK services imports for four quarters to the end of March 2022. The UK’s top 5 trading partners for imports of goods in 2021 are China, Germany, the United States, the Netherlands, and Norway. </p><table><thead><tr><th><strong>Top</strong> <strong>5</strong> <strong>UK goods   imports</strong></th><th><strong>Value (£   billion)</strong></th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>Gas</td><td>39.9</td></tr><tr><td>Cars</td><td>32.8</td></tr><tr><td>Medicinal and  pharmaceutical products</td><td>28.1</td></tr><tr><td>Crude oil</td><td>28.0</td></tr><tr><td>Refined oil</td><td>22.7</td></tr></tbody></table><table><thead><tr><th><strong>Top 5 UK services imports</strong></th><th><strong>Value (£   billion)</strong></th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>Other business  services</td><td>79.9</td></tr><tr><td>Transport  services</td><td>23.3</td></tr><tr><td>Travel services</td><td>19.6</td></tr><tr><td>Financial  services</td><td>16.9</td></tr><tr><td>Intellectual  property services</td><td>12.8</td></tr></tbody></table><h4 id="3-Balance-of-payment-situation"><a href="#3-Balance-of-payment-situation" class="headerlink" title="3. Balance of payment situation:"></a>3. Balance of payment situation:</h4><p>The balance of payments is the record of all international financial transactions made by a country’s residents, including the current account, the capital account, and the financial account. All trades conducted by private and public sectors are accounted for in the BOP to determine how much money is going in and out of a country. The data published by the International Monetary Fund has shown the BOP of the current account balance from the year 1970 to 2021(Bank, 2022). From 1997 till now, the UK has been in a current account deficit condition. The current account deficit is a measurement of a country’s trade where the value of the goods and services it imports exceeds the value of the products it exports.</p><h4 id="4-Exchange-rates"><a href="#4-Exchange-rates" class="headerlink" title="4. Exchange rates"></a>4. Exchange rates</h4><p>The UK is a floating exchange rate regime in which the price of a country’s currency is determined by the foreign exchange markets. It is based on the supply and demand of one currency relative to another. The United Kingdom entered the floating exchange rate regime in 1972, along with most other countries in the world, leaving the Bretton Woods system behind. The current rate of exchange on October 18th of the British Pound to the Chinese Yuan is 8.165. And the overall exchange rate for the past year has declined from around 8.8 in October 2021 to 8.1 in October 2022(Barchart, 2022).     </p><p><img src="/img/eco-1.jpeg" alt="eco-1"></p><h3 id="L-Trade-Restriction"><a href="#L-Trade-Restriction" class="headerlink" title="L: Trade Restriction"></a>L: Trade Restriction</h3><h4 id="1-Embargoes"><a href="#1-Embargoes" class="headerlink" title="1. Embargoes:"></a>1. Embargoes:</h4><p>There are 38 trade barriers from the UK to China for example sectors like food and drink, healthcare services, pharmaceuticals and biotechnology etc. In the food and drink sector, the UK has not permitted cherries, lamb meat, and hops to export to China(Government.UK, 2020). There is also a partial arms embargo on China, and the military items covered by the embargo are lethal weapons Field(Government.UK, December, 2020) such as machine guns, large-caliber weapons, bombs, torpedoes, rockets and missiles. </p><h4 id="2-Quotas"><a href="#2-Quotas" class="headerlink" title="2. Quotas:"></a>2. Quotas:</h4><p>We can look at the UK tariff rate quotas for 2022. In the commodity part, there is poultry, pigment, cereals, olive oil, rice, beef, garlic, sugar, milk products, and eggs(Government.UK, 2022b). There is an order number and annual quantity available for each order, and it can be divided into 4 sub-periods of the available quantity. For more information visit the website of the UK trade quotas(Government.UK, 2022c).</p><h4 id="3-Import-taxes"><a href="#3-Import-taxes" class="headerlink" title="3. Import taxes:"></a>3. Import taxes:</h4><p>UK import tax will vary depending on several factors, including the type of item sent, the value, the country of origin, and the intended use including personal or commercial. You pay VAT when you buy the goods or to the delivery company before you receive them. VAT is not charged on goods that are gifts worth £39 or less. If you have to pay VAT to the delivery company, it’s charged on the total package value, including the value of the goods postage, packaging and insurance, and any duty you owe. You will need to pay VAT to the delivery company if the goods are gifts sent to you by someone else and worth more than £39 and the excise goods(Government.UK, 2022a).</p><h4 id="4-Tariffs"><a href="#4-Tariffs" class="headerlink" title="4. Tariffs:"></a>4. Tariffs:</h4><p>The UK Global Tariff (UKGT) is the UK’s first independent tariff policy which replaced the EU Common External Tariff (CET) which applied until 31 December 2020. This tariff entered into force on 1 January 2021. The Government has published the UK Global Tariff (UKGT) which applies to all goods imported unless:</p><ul><li>the country imports come from has a preferential <a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/collections/the-uks-trade-agreements">trade agreement</a></li><li>an exception applies, such as a relief or <a href="https://www.gov.uk/guidance/duty-suspensions-and-tariff-quotas">tariff suspension</a></li><li>the goods come from developing countries covered by the <a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/trading-with-developing-nations">Generalised Scheme of Preferences</a></li></ul><h4 id="5-Licensing"><a href="#5-Licensing" class="headerlink" title="5. Licensing:"></a>5. Licensing:</h4><p>The UK Government Licensing Framework (UKGLF) provides a policy and legal overview of the arrangements for licensing the use and re-use of public sector information both in the central government and the wider public sector. It sets out best practices and standardizes licensing principles. In the context of the UKGLF, the licenses ensure that users are aware of the need to use the information responsibly and not in ways that mislead others. The UKGLF provides a coherent standard approach to licensing through a portfolio of licensing solutions developed to cover the following situations field (Archives, 2016).</p><ul><li><p>Free use and re-use for all purposes both commercial and non-commercial-the Open Government Licence</p></li><li><p>Free use and re-use for non-commercial purposes only-the Non-Commercial Government Licence</p></li><li><p>Where charges are made for the re-use of information, including in the context of s102 of the Protection of Freedoms Act 20121 and under the Re-use of Public Sector Information Regulations 2015-the Charged Licence </p></li></ul><h4 id="6-Customs-duties"><a href="#6-Customs-duties" class="headerlink" title="6. Customs duties:"></a>6. Customs duties:</h4><p>You’ll be charged Customs Duty on all goods sent from outside the UK (or the UK and the EU if you’re in Northern Ireland) if they’re either excise goods or worth more than £135. If you’re charged Customs Duty, you’ll need to pay it on both the price paid for the goods; postage, packaging, and insurance. In the UK you pay Customs Duty on excise goods of any value</p><table><thead><tr><th>Non-excise goods worth £135 or less</th><th>No charge</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>Gifts above £135  and up to £630</td><td>2.5%, but rates  are lower for some goods</td></tr><tr><td>Gifts above £630  and other goods above £135</td><td>The rate depends  on the type of goods and where they came from</td></tr></tbody></table><h3 id="M-Extent-of-economic-activity-not-included-in-cash-income-activities"><a href="#M-Extent-of-economic-activity-not-included-in-cash-income-activities" class="headerlink" title="M: Extent of economic activity not included in cash income activities"></a>M: Extent of economic activity not included in cash income activities</h3><h4 id="1-Countertrades"><a href="#1-Countertrades" class="headerlink" title="1. Countertrades:"></a>1. Countertrades:</h4><p>Many governments reduce imbalances in trade between countries using a countertrade system of international trading. Companies that consider countertrade typically want to expand into a foreign market, increase sales, build customer and supplier relationships, and overcome liquidity challenges. This type of international trade is more common in developing countries with limited foreign exchange or credit facilities. </p><p>Countertrade can be classified into three broad categories: barter, counterpurchase, and offset. Bartering is the oldest countertrade arrangement. It is the direct exchange of goods and services with an equivalent value but with no cash settlement. For example, a bag of nuts might be exchanged for coffee beans or meat. Under a counterpurchase arrangement, the exporter sells goods or services to an importer and agrees to also purchase other goods from the importer within a specified period. The exporters entering into a counterpurchase arrangement must use a trading firm to sell the goods they purchase and will not use the goods themselves. In an offset arrangement, the seller assists in marketing products manufactured by the buying country or allows part of the exported product’s assembly to be carried out by manufacturers in the buying country. This practice is common in aerospace, defense and certain infrastructure industries.</p><h4 id="2-Foreign-aid-received"><a href="#2-Foreign-aid-received" class="headerlink" title="2. Foreign aid received:"></a>2. Foreign aid received:</h4><p>The UK’s trading relationships with developing countries positively impact UK consumers by providing a wider choice of everyday goods at lower costs, making household incomes go further. For UK businesses, imports from developing countries support UK exports. For example, according to UN Comtrade data, in 2016, 48% of UK imports of un-processed tea came from Kenya, 10% of imports of prepared fish came from Ghana, and 21% of T-shirts came from Bangladesh. By helping developing countries trade more with the UK and the rest of the world, the UK can support their economic development which helps drive growth and jobs in a way that aid-spending alone cannot (Lee, 2018). </p><h3 id="N-Labor-force"><a href="#N-Labor-force" class="headerlink" title="N: Labor force"></a>N: Labor force</h3><h4 id="1-Size"><a href="#1-Size" class="headerlink" title="1. Size:"></a>1. Size:</h4><p>The employment rate has decreased since the start of the coronavirus pandemic, and it increased at the end of 2020. However, the employment rate decreased from June to August 2022, and self-employed workers increased. Compared with the previous three-month period from March to May 2022 which had a higher employment rate than other recent periods(Statistics, 2022). </p><p><img src="/img/eco2.jpeg" alt="eco2"></p><h4 id="2-Unemployment-rates"><a href="#2-Unemployment-rates" class="headerlink" title="2. Unemployment rates:"></a>2. Unemployment rates:</h4><p>The unemployment rate had generally been falling since late 2013 until the start of the COVID-19 pandemic. It increased until the end of 2020 but has now returned to pre-coronavirus pandemic levels. Over the latest three-month period, the unemployment rate decreased to the lowest rate of around 3.5%.</p><p><img src="/img/eco3.jpeg" alt="eco3"></p><h3 id="O-Inflation-rates"><a href="#O-Inflation-rates" class="headerlink" title="O: Inflation rates:"></a>O: Inflation rates:</h3><p>The inflation rate in the United Kingdom was 10.1 percent in September 2022, compared with 9.9 percent in August 2022. This is the joint-highest inflation rate recorded for the Consumer Price Index (CPI) in the UK, with prices also rising by 10.1 percent a few weeks earlier in July 2022 (Statistica, 2022). During the most recent month, housing costs, such as energy and water, had the most significant price increases. </p><p><img src="/img/eco4.jpeg" alt="eco4"></p><p>Reference:</p><p>Archives, N. (2016). UK government Licensing Framework. <a href="https://cdn.nationalarchives.gov.uk/documents/information-management/uk-government-licensing-framework.pdf">https://cdn.nationalarchives.gov.uk/documents/information-management/uk-government-licensing-framework.pdf</a> </p><p>Bank, T. W. (2022). <em>Current account balance (BoP, current US$) - United Kingdom</em>. <a href="https://data.worldbank.org/indicator/BN.CAB.XOKA.CD?end=2021&amp;locations=GB&amp;start=1970">https://data.worldbank.org/indicator/BN.CAB.XOKA.CD?end=2021&amp;locations=GB&amp;start=1970</a></p><p>Barchart. (2022). <em>British Pound to Chinese Yuan</em> <a href="https://www.barchart.com/forex/quotes/^GBPCNY/overview">https://www.barchart.com/forex/quotes/%5EGBPCNY/overview</a></p><p>Government.UK. (2020). <em>Trade barriers in China</em>. <a href="https://www.check-international-trade-barriers.service.gov.uk/barriers/?resolved=0&amp;location=cn">https://www.check-international-trade-barriers.service.gov.uk/barriers/?resolved=0&amp;location=cn</a></p><p>Government.UK. (2022a). <em>Tax and customs for goods sent from abroad</em>. <a href="https://www.gov.uk/goods-sent-from-abroad/tax-and-duty">https://www.gov.uk/goods-sent-from-abroad/tax-and-duty</a></p><p>Government.UK. (2022b). <em>UK tariff rate quotas 2022</em>. <a href="https://www.gov.uk/guidance/uk-tariff-rate-quotas-2022">https://www.gov.uk/guidance/uk-tariff-rate-quotas-2022</a></p><p>Government.UK. (2022c). UK trade quotas. <a href="https://data.api.trade.gov.uk/v1/datasets/uk-trade-quotas/versions/v1.0.22/metadata?format=html">https://data.api.trade.gov.uk/v1/datasets/uk-trade-quotas/versions/v1.0.22/metadata?format=html</a> </p><p>Government.UK. (December, 2020). <em>UK arms embargo on mainland China and Hong Kong</em>. <a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/collections/uk-arms-embargo-on-mainland-china-and-hong-kong">https://www.gov.uk/government/collections/uk-arms-embargo-on-mainland-china-and-hong-kong</a></p><p>Lee, J. (2018). <em>Aid and trade</em>. <a href="https://una.org.uk/magazine/2018-1/aid-and-trade">https://una.org.uk/magazine/2018-1/aid-and-trade</a></p><p>Statistica. (2022). <em>Inflation rate for the Consumer Price Index (CPI) in the United Kingdom from January 1989 to September 2022</em>. <a href="https://www.statista.com/statistics/306648/inflation-rate-consumer-price-index-cpi-united-kingdom-uk/">https://www.statista.com/statistics/306648/inflation-rate-consumer-price-index-cpi-united-kingdom-uk/</a></p><p>Statistics, N. (2022). <em>Employment in the UK: October 2022</em>. <a href="https://www.ons.gov.uk/employmentandlabourmarket/peopleinwork/employmentandemployeetypes/bulletins/employmentintheuk/latest">https://www.ons.gov.uk/employmentandlabourmarket/peopleinwork/employmentandemployeetypes/bulletins/employmentintheuk/latest</a></p><p>Statistics, N. (September 2022). <em>UK trade: July 2022</em>. <a href="https://www.ons.gov.uk/economy/nationalaccounts/balanceofpayments/bulletins/uktrade/july2022">https://www.ons.gov.uk/economy/nationalaccounts/balanceofpayments/bulletins/uktrade/july2022</a></p><p>Statistics, O. (October 2022). <em>UK trade in numbers</em> <a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/statistics/uk-trade-in-numbers/uk-trade-in-numbers-web-version#import-statistics">https://www.gov.uk/government/statistics/uk-trade-in-numbers/uk-trade-in-numbers-web-version#import-statistics</a> </p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>Trade</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Uk&#39;s Political system</title>
    <link href="/2022/09/23/UK_political_system/"/>
    <url>/2022/09/23/UK_political_system/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><u>Summary:</u> </p><p>The British political system is a two-party system and in order to measure a country’s political stability, we can look at the indicator of the political stability index. The latest data from 2020 shows that the UK scores 0.47 which proves that the UK has a relatively stable government compared with the average level in the world. The 2022 International IP shows the UK has ranked No.2 out of the 55 economies which indicates that the UK has a mature law and supervision system to continue to promote and develop the intellectual property market. The fundamental principles of business culture in the United Kingdom are courtesy, politeness, discipline, and punctuality and most British businesspeople are following a rational and pragmatic approach.</p><p><strong>C: Political system</strong></p><p><strong>Political structure:</strong> Britain is a constitutional monarchy governed by a king or a queen and it is also a parliamentary democracy whose government is controlled by a parliament that has been elected by the people. The highest positions in the government are filled by the members of the directly elected parliament.</p><p><strong>Political parties:</strong> The British political system is a two-party system. Since the 1920s, the two dominant parties have been the Conservative Party and the Labour Party. In September of 2022, Liz Truss became the new prime minister of the UK after meeting the queen at Balmoral. Her first significant act as prime minister is to deal with the high price of energy and made it affordable to the people of the UK. </p><p>Stability of the government: To measure a country’s political stability, we can look at the indicator of the political stability index. It ranges in degree from -2.5 meaning unstable to +2.5 which means stable. The given data shows from the year 1996 to 2020, the average value for the United Kingdom was 0.48. With a minimum of 0.08 points in 2018 and a maximum of 1.04 points in 2000. In the latest data from 2020, the world average value based on 194 countries is -0.07, and the UK scores 0.47 (Bank, 2020).  The compared result proves that the UK has a relatively stable government with better performance than the average level in the world. A general conclusion can be obtained through this observation from the British government. The stable political environment is of great opportunity to expand our market in this country.</p><p><strong>Special taxes in the UK:</strong></p><p>In 2021/22, the UK government raised over £915 billion a year in receipts – income from taxes and other sources. This is equivalent to around 39% of the size of the UK economy, as measured by GDP. In cash terms, the hardest hit tax in 2020/21 was VAT, where receipts were over £17 billion lower, compared with 2019/20. Consumers were less able to go out and spend during the pandemic, and Government policies, such as cutting VAT from 20% to 5% for the ‘hospitality, accommodation, and attractions sector, have also affected VAT receipt (Matthew, 2022).  </p><p>For example, the carbon tax. A Carbon tax aims to make individuals and firms pay the full social cost of carbon pollution. This special tax will encourage individuals to reduce pollution and encourage them to use more environmentally products such as solar power. It also makes polluters pay the external cost of carbon emissions. In contrast, there exist some problems, for example, enterprises may avoid paying carbon tax by secretly polluting the greenhouse gases in the environment (Pettinger, 2020 ). Under this scenario, the government should strengthen education on ethical behavior and set guidelines and regulations for the people to follow.</p><p><strong>Local government:</strong> Normally, Government is responsible for deciding how the country is run, they set taxes, and deciding how to best deliver public services such as the National Health Service, and welfare benefits such as the state pension. In the United Kingdom, Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland have their devolved governments and each with varying powers. The parliament’s job is to look closely at the Government’s plans and to monitor the way they are running things, they work on behalf of the government’s decision by examining new proposals closely and suggesting improvements, checking how public money is being spent, and tracking how new laws are working out in practice (Parliament, 2022). </p><p><strong>D: Legal system</strong></p><p><strong>Judiciary system:</strong> The UK does not have a constitution that is contained in a written constitutional instrument. It is to be found in the statutes passed by Parliament and in the common law, which developed over historical reasons. As a state made up of several separate jurisdictions, the United Kingdom does not have a single unified legal system. The UK lacks a written constitution on the current political and legal institutions, also their institutions did not separate the functions and powers of the three different branches of the state which are the executive, the legislature, and the judiciary (Judiciary, 2022). </p><p>For example, the government is made up of MPs and peers who are also members of the legislature including the House of Commons and the House of Lords. The UK public elects 650 Members of Parliament to represent their interests and concerns in the House of Commons. The House of Lords is the second chamber of the UK Parliament. It plays a crucial role in examining bills, questioning government action, and investigating public policy. In this case, it is usually quite intricate and requires some time to make a unified decision or pass through the law such as the Brexit issue. If a company wants to do business in the UK it would be better to choose a time after the factionalism.</p><p><strong>Intellectual property</strong>: IP usually gives the creator an exclusive right over the use of his creation for a certain period. Copyright, patents, designs, and trademarks are common rights for intellectual property protection. 179 countries have signed up to the Berne Convention which lays down a common framework and agreement between nations concerning intellectual property rights. The 2022 International IP Index published by the US Chamber of Commerce has given out the rankings and the indicators of the overall score of IP. The UK has ranked No.2 out of the 55 economies. It has a high ranking in the sector of copyright and trademark and a relatively lower ranking in the patents and design rights (commerce, 2022). Copyright law originated in the United Kingdom from a concept of common law which is the Statute of Anne 1709. It became statutory with the passing of the Copyright Act of 1911. The current act is the Copyright, Designs, and Patents Act 1988(service, 2022). The UK has a mature law and supervision system to continue to promote and develop the intellectual property market. </p><p><strong>E: Social Organization</strong></p><p><strong>Group behavior:</strong> Social organization refers to the network of relationships in a group and how they interconnect with each other. For example, Social Value UK is a Joint Member Network of Social Value International, the global standard-setting organization for social value and impact management. Social Value International has also partnered with the UNDP and SDG Impact to support the adoption of the SDG Impact Standards globally. Social Value UK’s mission is to change the way society accounts for value through principles, practice, people, and power and develop guidance, tools, and support to help achieve the principles. Businesses can make a cooperation with these organizations and achieve common goals to enhance customers’ favorability and their reputation. </p><p><strong>The UK social classes:</strong> </p><p>Approximated Social Grade with its six categories A, B, C1, C2, D, and E is a socio-economic classification produced by the ONS (UK Office for National Statistics) by applying an algorithm developed by members of the MRS Census &amp; Geodemographics Group. It applies to every Household Reference Person (HRP) aged 16 to 64 (Geographics, 2014). </p><table><thead><tr><th>Social Grade</th><th>Description</th><th>% HRP population (UK)</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>AB</td><td>Higher &amp; intermediate managerial,  administrative, professional occupations</td><td>22.17</td></tr><tr><td>C1</td><td>Supervisory, clerical &amp; junior managerial,  administrative, professional occupations</td><td>30.84</td></tr><tr><td>C2</td><td>Skilled manual occupations</td><td>20.94</td></tr><tr><td>DE</td><td>Semi-skilled &amp; unskilled manual occupations,  Unemployed and lowest grade occupations</td><td>26.05</td></tr></tbody></table><p>From the data in the table, we can tell more than half of the proportion of people in the UK are in the middle class and above. It is clear for the company to target its customer to a specific group of social classes.</p><p><strong>Clubs:</strong> The Equality Act 2010 brings together harmonizes, in some respects extends previous equality laws. It aims to make it more consistent, clearer, and easier to follow, to make society fairer. The Act protects people from discrimination based on protected characteristics. Examples of associations include private clubs such as golf and other sports clubs, ex-forces clubs, alumni clubs, social clubs, working men’s clubs, gaming clubs, and drinking clubs. Some charities also meet the definition of an association, for example, the Scout Association and Girlguiding UK. Such charities are also subject to additional provisions relating to the provision of charitable benefits.</p><p><strong>Subcultures:</strong> Since 2001, the foreign-born share of the population has doubled to about nine million. Meanwhile, the number of those from an ethnic minority background, including ‘White Other’, has more than doubled to over 13 million, their share of the population rising from 10% to 21%. Just over one-third of all births now involve at least one foreign-born parent and one in three pupils in English state-funded schools are from an ethnic minority background. The (UK, 2021) Gaming and non-mainstream religious groups are the two leading subcultures in the UK today, according to research that highlights the value to marketers of tapping into niche cultural groups. (WARC, 2020) Overall, 73% connect with subcultures virtually. And of those online-only connectors, two-thirds are younger (67% are under 44) and are more likely to connect to gaming, body modification, fandom, and influencer subcultures. YouTube is the main platform for contact (38%) and Facebook communities remain at the heart of subculture involvement. Understanding the subcultures can be useful for the business to understand and better adapt to the local market.</p><p><strong>F: Business customs and practices</strong></p><p>The fundamental principles of business culture in the United Kingdom are courtesy, politeness, discipline, and punctuality. Most British businesspeople are following a rational and pragmatic approach. Only on rare occasions, a commitment is announced right away, while agreements need to be formalized in writing. Due to the high frequency of meetings, people working in an office environment are often away from their desks. (Expatica, 2022) This accounts for the comparatively high number of memos sent and received in a UK company. So, we need to arrange appointments in advance. Dress codes in the UK are still comparatively strict. Colleagues appreciate a sense of fashion and quality. While men wear suits, ties, and striped or colored shirts and black shoes while women wear suits with trousers or skirts or normally in dresses, often with high heels. In most companies, colleagues enjoy an after-work drink together on a Friday night. Apart from this custom, the tendency is to keep work and private life strictly separated. Invitations to someone’s private home are gestures of affection and sympathy, which is uncommon between mere business partners. Colleagues exchange business cards before or at the beginning of a meeting. A card usually displays someone’s job title, first and surname. Academic titles are not necessarily on a business card unless they are relevant to your work. It is essentially important to understand its local customs when doing business with the British people. </p><p><strong>Reference:</strong></p><p>Bank, T. W. (2020). <em>United Kingdom: Political stability</em>. <a href="https://www.theglobaleconomy.com/United-Kingdom/wb_political_stability/">https://www.theglobaleconomy.com/United-Kingdom/wb_political_stability/</a></p><p>commerce, U. c. o. (2022). <em>International IP Index</em>. <a href="https://www.uschamber.com/assets/documents/IPIndex-FullReport_2022.pdf.pdf#asset:185047@1">https://www.uschamber.com/assets/documents/IPIndex-FullReport_2022.pdf.pdf#asset:185047@1</a></p><p>Expatica. (2022). <em>Business culture in the United Kingdom</em>. <a href="https://www.expatica.com/uk/working/employment-basics/uk-business-culture-103182/?__cf_chl_tk=N8dWYGcvfYKJg1HMN3Ge6rUGR_mAA.p6eRTck0ccB3U-1664037962-0-gaNycGzNDGU">https://www.expatica.com/uk/working/employment-basics/uk-business-culture-103182/?__cf_chl_tk=N8dWYGcvfYKJg1HMN3Ge6rUGR_mAA.p6eRTck0ccB3U-1664037962-0-gaNycGzNDGU</a></p><p>Geographics, U. (2014). <em>Social Grade</em>. <a href="https://www.ukgeographics.co.uk/blog/social-grade-a-b-c1-c2-d-e">https://www.ukgeographics.co.uk/blog/social-grade-a-b-c1-c2-d-e</a></p><p>Judiciary. (2022). The justice system and the constitution. <a href="https://www.judiciary.uk/about-the-judiciary/our-justice-system/jud-acc-ind/justice-sys-and-constitution/">https://www.judiciary.uk/about-the-judiciary/our-justice-system/jud-acc-ind/justice-sys-and-constitution/</a> </p><p>Matthew. (2022). <em>Tax statistics: an overview</em>. <a href="https://researchbriefings.files.parliament.uk/documents/CBP-8513/CBP-8513.pdf">https://researchbriefings.files.parliament.uk/documents/CBP-8513/CBP-8513.pdf</a></p><p>Parliament, U. (2022). <em>Parliament and the Government</em>. <a href="https://www.parliament.uk/about/how/role/relations-with-other-institutions/parliament-government/">https://www.parliament.uk/about/how/role/relations-with-other-institutions/parliament-government/</a></p><p>Pettinger, T. (2020 ). <em>Carbon Tax – Pros and Cons</em>. <a href="https://www.economicshelp.org/blog/2207/economics/carbon-tax-pros-and-cons/">https://www.economicshelp.org/blog/2207/economics/carbon-tax-pros-and-cons/</a></p><p>service, U. c. r. (2022). <em>UK Copyright Law</em>. <a href="https://copyrightservice.co.uk/copyright/p01_uk_copyright_law">https://copyrightservice.co.uk/copyright/p01_uk_copyright_law</a></p><p>UK, M. W. (2021). <em>Impact of immigration in changing the UK population</em>. <a href="https://www.migrationwatchuk.org/briefing-paper/492/impact-of-immigration-in-changing-the-uk-population">https://www.migrationwatchuk.org/briefing-paper/492/impact-of-immigration-in-changing-the-uk-population</a></p><p>WARC. (2020). <em>UK subcultures are alive and well</em>. <a href="https://www.warc.com/newsandopinion/news/uk-subcultures-are-alive-and-well/en-gb/43997">https://www.warc.com/newsandopinion/news/uk-subcultures-are-alive-and-well/en-gb/43997</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>Politics</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Hello, my distinguished guest</title>
    <link href="/2022/09/23/hello/"/>
    <url>/2022/09/23/hello/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hi 👋, I am Diana Zhang</p><p>Welcome to my blog :)</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>Misc</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
</search>
